(This show features indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
- It's windy. - It's so cool.
- It's cool and nice. - It's breezy.
(As the heat has finally eased up,)
The weather is great.
(it's the perfect weather for a workout.)
(A gym in Euljiro)
- What is this? - It's a gym.
- What is this place? - I didn't know there was a gym.
- This is a gym. - It smells like a gym in here.
(Happy)
- Hello. - I didn't know of this place.
(Clocking in in workout gear)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Was there a gym here? - Okay!
(Touching)
- All right. - My goodness. What is this place?
- Your body is quite solid. - Sure.
He's rock-solid.
(The fit 60-year-old basks in the compliment.)
Okay. I didn't work out yesterday.
- Still, it's solid as a rock. - I know.
Seok Jin, your face looks bloated today.
- It's just fat. - What did you say, you punk?
- Your face is puffy. - I ate tteokbokki yesterday.
(Upset)
- Tteokbokki? - I ate tteokbokki yesterday.
It's really puffy.
(Smiling)
- He looks good, though. - Right. He looks great.
Right. You eat well when you're healthy.
Seok Jin, now that you've filled out a bit,
- your skin looks glowing. - That's true.
(Tteokbokki botox)
- Are you serious? - Yes, your skin looks great.
- Your skin looks smooth. - He's pleased.
- He doesn't have wrinkles. - I see.
- Your skin looks tight. - He looks like he's 60.
(Spoiling the mood)
You darn brat.
- Don't say things you don't mean. - His skin is really tight.
(Kicking)
You don't look like you're 60.
He looks 60 years old from behind.
(Teasing behind his back)
- From behind? - He looks 60 years old from behind.
You look like you're 61.
(Teasing)
Hey!
By the way,
I watched this drama recently.
(His puffy face reminds him of a drama.)
- Which one? - It was...
- kind of like a thriller. - Okay.
The wife keeps making delicious food for her husband.
(Thriller)
(The carb killer from the drama "Love, ft. Marriage and Divorce")
She keeps asking, "Are you hungry?"
- Then she buys him pizza, - Is it a thriller?
cooks chicken dishes at night, and does things like that.
(After eating non-stop)
And in the end, the husband suddenly...
- He dies? - dies while watching a movie.
- From a stroke. - A stroke?
(A shocking development)
He dies like that. And three days ago,
my wife asked me to go and eat fried chicken with her.
(Getting goosebumps)
- So... - You've gained so much weight.
(No wonder.)
- Then... - I ate chicken late at night.
Why are you gaining so much weight lately?
I enjoyed the fried chicken a lot late at night.
(An intentional weight gain from fried chicken)
- And then yesterday, - Yesterday?
she went, "You're hungry, right?" and cooked up a lot of tteokbokki.
(A 2nd try with tteokbokki)
Seriously, your face gained a ton of weight.
I just couldn't stop thinking about that drama.
Your wife must've watched that drama too.
I guess she's looking to start a brand-new life.
That can't be it, but she keeps feeding me recently.
(Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong's thrilling everyday life)
- She does? - Just like the drama.
Even your nose got chubby.
- I've gained weight. - Your face is all swollen up.
What?
- What? - Haha?
("Haha, an Offer to Star in a Hollywood Blockbuster?")
He got an offer for a Hollywood blockbuster?
- He's lying. - That must be a lie.
- You're lying. - Don't you dare fool us.
(Nodding)
- That's just ridiculous. - What was that?
Why is he trying to build this kind of fake image?
(Showing off)
- Should I really reveal what it is? - What is it?
- Don't be absurd. - Spit it out.
(It sounds unreal, but Hollywood did offer him a role.)
- What happened? - Don't mention it...
until you're officially cast and start filming the movie.
(No one can accept it.)
- You just got an offer. - I just...
(What's the Hollywood movie that chose Haha?)
- What's the movie? - Tell us about the project.
What's the title?
It's "The Lord of the Rings."
- What? - Are you Gollum?
(Immediately)
You're a hobbit.
- That's right. - Are you really a hobbit?
- You're a hobbit. - That's right.
(A real hobbit?)
- Hobbit? - Are you really a hobbit?
An Asian hobbit.
A real hobbit?
(Korean hobbit recognized by the whole world)
A hobbit who doesn't even need special effects makeup.
Yes. I was offered to play 1 of the 12 hobbits.
(The main hobbit)
- A hobbit? - An Asian hobbit.
(Probably something like this?)
- Are you serious? - You do look like a hobbit.
- And... - Haha is a perfect fit.
Like hobbits, he has huge feet.
That's true. I don't need any makeup.
(Even the giant feet that save on costume costs)
- Look at his feet. - He wouldn't need any makeup.
That's unbelievable.
(Will we see a proudly representing K-hobbit...)
I was asked to play an Asian hobbit.
- Are you serious? - You do look like a hobbit.
(in "The Lord of the Rings?")
So I took my profile photos and sent them,
(Bursting into laughter)
and they told me to clear my schedule for a month.
("The Lord of the Rings:" Are you free for one month?)
But I told them, "I'm sorry, but Running Man is my top priority."
("Sorry, Running Man comes first." From the K-hobbit)
I turned it down because of this show.
- You turned it down? - I did.
(Yes.)
- Are you serious? - You turned it down?
(You turned down "The Lord of the Rings?")
The original "The Lord of the Rings?"
- You should've done it. - The original one?
- The one with the whole main cast. - You should've done it.
There's not much difference whether you're here or not.
(What?)
- You should've accepted it. - We will let you go.
Everything will be fine.
(Even without you)
- You have to do it. - Why did you turn it down?
(The six members are berserk at Hobbit Ha's decision.)
Why did you not accept the offer?
- Tell them you're in. - Why did you turn it down?
(Disappointed by the reaction, different from what he expected)
I was really planning to do it,
- but I turned it down. - Unbelievable.
Wasn't it some cheap knockoff, by any chance?
Like. "The Lord of the First Birthday Rings?"
(Defamation)
What? The first birthday ring?
Or maybe "The Lord of the Semi-basement."
("The Lord of the Semi-basement")
- Semi-basement. - They live in the basement.
Are you sure it was "The Lord of the Rings?"
(Today's Running Man with "The Lord of the Semi-basement")
- Semi-basement. - Semi-basement?
Before we start,
- I have something to tell you. - What is it?
The viewers have prepared one-of-a-kind award certificates...
to honor the Running Man members on your 16th anniversary.
What award?
This was from an event we hosted on Instagram last month.
(Handmade awards by the viewers through a social media event)
Out of thousands of submissions,
(Jee Seok Jin: Screen Time Struggle Award)
(Yu Jae Seok: Yu-mes Bond Award)
only 7 certificates were selected to be presented to you all.
(Song Ji Hyo: One Punch Award)
- Really? - Seok Sam...
Do you have award certificates for each member?
(Excited)
- Yes. One for each. - Really?
- What? - Award certificate.
(Viewer-Voted Running Man Awards)
The Ancestor Award, Jee Seok Jin.
- Is the name of the award Ancestor? - It's called the Ancestor Award?
- The Ancestor Award. - "As a living fossil..."
- "of variety shows..." - Ancestor?
"and the oldest living ancestor of Running Man,"
(For his unmatched dedication and tireless effort as...)
"he has delivered slapstick comedy like a walking jointed doll..."
(Running Man's oldest member)
(Ancestor Award for Ancestor Seok Sam)
"every single week, and is therefore awarded this certificate."
"Presented by the viewers of Running Man."
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
(Amazed)
Is it really called the Ancestor Award?
The citation is out of the ordinary, so I love it even more.
- Next. - What could it be?
- The Monster Award. - The Monster Award.
- It's for Jong Kook. - The Monster Award.
- He's a monstrous man. - "Just like his love for soccer..."
"despite being terrible at it,"
"and just like his love for the members..."
(Has love for the members, rock-solid muscles,)
- "despite hiding his feelings," - That's true.
"though his expressions may be unique,"
(and superhuman strength)
"he has protected and cherished Running Man for 16 years..."
"with his rock-solid muscles and monstrous strength,"
(A special award for the tough-on-the-outside,)
"he is therefore awarded this award."
(soft-on-the-inside, Jong Kook)
- The Monster Award. - Congratulations.
The Monster Award!
(Thankful)
- The Ancestor Award! - Next.
The Fantasy Award. Song Ji Hyo.
- The Fantasy Award? - The Fantasy Award?
"Whenever captured on screen,"
(Full of surprises from a fantastically talented actress...)
"she showcases her top-tier main-job brilliance..."
"with her breathtaking, jaw-dropping looks,"
"yet transforms at times into the hot-tempered Bad Ji Hyo..."
(to the fiery Bad Ji Hyo)
"to whip the members into shape,"
"which delivers fantastic catharsis to viewers through her charms,"
- "and is awarded this certificate." - That's so nice.
- They wrote amazing citations. - It's so good.
That sounds amazing.
I'm so thankful.
Next.
- It's for Ye Eun. - What is it?
The Korean Cuisine and Dining Award.
Isn't Choi Bul Am supposed to be presenting this award?
- This is funny. - "No matter..."
"what menu is served, she seizes every opportunity..."
(A true foodie who's never complained about a single side dish)
"to stuff her mouth..."
"and stimulate the viewers' salivary glands,"
"and is therefore awarded this certificate."
(The best compliment for Ms. Free Meals)
- Your award sounds great. - Thank you.
- I love it. - The fonts are big.
- Yes, it's really big. - I wonder what I'm getting.
(Excited)
Nice. The Korean Cuisine and Dining Award.
Next up is Yang Se Chan.
- What is the award called? - What is it?
- What? - For being ugly?
(Startled)
The Grand Duke of the Belly Award.
- The Grand Duke of the Belly Award? - The Grand Duke of the Belly Award?
"Rather than sharp, Grand-Duke-of-the-North-like looks,"
(Grand Duke of the Belly has won over fans...)
"he has united all fans with his pale, soft-tofu-like belly,"
(with his soft, tofu-like belly.)
"and is therefore awarded this certificate."
- I should show it to the viewers. - The Grand Duke of the Belly Award.
(Pulling up)
Like this.
- The Grand Duke of the Belly Award. - How does he manage...
to maintain the belly all the time?
- I wonder what I'm receiving. - All right.
(Jealous)
- Next up is Haha. - Haha.
- The Weather Phenomenon Award. - The Weather Phenomenon Award.
"Rain or shine, he has appeared in every single episode,"
"naturally blending into our daily lives..."
(Never missed a single day in 16 years)
"for 16 years just like the ever-changing weather,"
(A special commendation for this true icon of dedication)
"and is therefore awarded this certificate."
It's okay for him to miss an episode, though.
Right. You can take a one-month break.
(Secured his perfect attendance even despite Hollywood's temptations)
You've done this so faithfully all this time,
- so one month is totally fine. - Right.
- What was it again? - The Weather Phenomenon Award.
- It's me. - It's our Grasshopper.
(Finally, it's Jae Seok's turn.)
- The Myriad Faces Award. - The Myriad Faces Award.
- The Myriad Faces Award. - "Though possessing..."
"well-aligned facial features,"
(Running Man's irreplaceable pillar with unmatched presence and looks)
"he delivers a uniquely unharmonious visual,"
"and despite exuding a colossal aura that commands the entire shoot,"
(A giant aura with an adorably tiny, petty side)
"he simultaneously reveals an unfittingly tiny, petty side."
"Since he has showcased his 1,000 grand moments..."
"and 10,000 hilariously tiny sides over the past 16 years,"
"he is hereby presented with this certificate."
(Using his killer move)
- Are you happy now? - That's funny.
(Wrapping up the awards ceremony on a happy note...)
- Did you like it? - It was really funny.
(with the eldest's playful antics)
- "He is hereby presented." - "He is hereby presented."
"He is hereby presented."
- "He is hereby presented." - Thank you so much.
(Thank you for the heartfelt awards.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Ancestor Award, Monster Award, The Fantasy Award,)
- I love The Dining Award. - They're good at this.
(The Korean Cuisine and Dining Award,)
They really are.
(The Grand Duke of the Belly Award...)
Just as you all received awards today,
we've prepared a special race where you can present a prize...
- to someone truly special. - Really?
- Jae Seok mentioned recently... - Yes?
after watching Cameraman Kang Chan Hee work...
(The camera boss)
that he deserved an Achievement Award.
(Jae Seok always said Chan Hee deserved an Achievement Award.)
- He does deserve one. - Right.
He should win an award at the Entertainment Awards Ceremony.
(2 weeks ago, after the shoot)
About Chan Hee...
- Chan Hee deserves an award. - What award?
He's been doing this job since the 1980s.
Chan Hee should receive an award at the Awards Ceremony.
(Director Kang Chan Hee,)
(who Jae Seok looked out for even after the shoot)
Where's Chan Hee?
- He went home. - He did?
(Whether he's around or not, the members always look for him.)
- The answer is Gang Gam Chan Hee. - Gam Chan Hee.
(The symbol of Running Man)
Gang Gam Chan Hee!
(A veteran who's been through a lot in Running Man for 16 years)
- Hurry. Let him out. - There you go.
Kang Chan Hee!
(The pillar of Running Man)
(The spiritual anchor of the production crew)
This is fun.
- Come here. - He's the captain.
(Chief Kang)
As I told you before,
even though I debuted back in 1991,
- Chan Hee started in the 1980s. - Right.
(Camera Director Kang Chan Hee)
- Okay? - That's unbelievable.
(Running Man, "Family Outing," "X-man," and more)
His name is officially rolling on the KBS end credits.
("2 Days 1 Night 4," "Happy Together," and more)
When I was about ten years into my career,
(In the past)
Chan Hee talked down to me,
- and I found it annoying. - Right.
I thought he was young.
How old were you when you started this job?
I joined the company in 1985.
- How old were you back then? - What?
How old were you?
I was 26 back then.
You were already 26 even back then?
(In 1985)
- In 1985? - What...
- I entered college in 1986. - I thought he started working...
in high school.
So you're five years older than Seok Jin, right?
(Yes.)
He looks amazingly youthful.
(A never-aging baby face)
- He looks really young for his age. - Five years.
He does have a young-looking face.
(Thinking)
- He looks really young. - Then, in a few years,
he'll turn 70.
- Seriously? - Yes.
- Can you believe it? - I mean, in a few years.
- Are you 70? - No.
(Shocked)
- Hey. - I see.
He will turn 70 later.
(Feeling a prick of conscience)
- Age is just a number. - He has five years left.
- He looks really young for his age. - He said...
- He said, "Age is just a number. - It's just a number.
That's true.
- Are you serious? - Am I wrong?
Then let's say you're younger than me.
(A younger brother who's 6 years older)
- Right. - I believe...
- age is more than a number. - Sure.
- You can be my little brother. - But I know your age.
(Junior Jee still wants to be treated as someone older.)
We've known each other for 30 years. We can't do that.
- We can't? - Chan Hee is really...
He looks unbelievably young.
- Cameraman Kang Chan Hee... - He really does.
has also been with the members for 16 full years,
(A race for Chief Kang, who has been with Running Man...)
- starting right from Episode One. - That's true.
(for 16 years since Episode 1)
- He's the living history. - Inspired by that,
we prepared today's race...
titled Stay Strong, Chief Kang!
(Chief Kang)
- What? - All right.
- I love it. - That sounds good.
To help our team's eldest member, Chan Hee,
regain his strength in this scorching summer,
we've prepared some nice gifts.
(Tailored gifts prepared just for Chief Kang)
- That's great. - We should give them to him.
(Joint supplement, Onnuri gift certificates,)
We haven't expressed our gratitude enough all this time.
(top-tier wild ginseng,)
(director's chair)
It's wild ginseng.
- There it is. - Onnuri gift certificates are nice.
(From the top-choice gift certificate...)
- This is it. - This is the best.
- That's the best one. - We have to get it.
- What is this? Wild ginseng? - It's wild ginseng.
(to the ultimate health-boosting top-tier wild ginseng)
- Onnuri gift certificates. - Wild ginseng.
What is this?
It's a chair with his name Kang Chan Hee...
- engraved on it. - It's a chair.
(Even a specially made director's chair for his tired back)
It's a chair for him.
- I see. - Nice.
- He doesn't have a chair? - This is nice.
- He's sitting on a box. - We should get him these.
- He's sitting on a box now. - No way.
(The much-needed chair)
- Sitting on a box? - Depending on how well...
- you perform, - You're right.
(All the gifts come with a catch.)
he can take home all of these amazing gifts...
(The gifts' destiny depends on the final result.)
- or none at all. - He should get all of them.
- It's up to us. - Let's do well.
(Burning with enthusiasm)
- We have to do well. - Let's do this.
In order to obtain the gifts,
you must defeat a professional dart player...
in games of darts.
- What? - A professional dart player?
- We... - Is there anyone in Korea?
Yes. We invited a professional dart player.
(Invited a real national dart team athlete)
How on earth are we supposed to beat a professional?
(100 points)
(The 16-year veteran members who step up when it counts...)
(and a professional dart player who shows no mercy)
He zeroed in.
Is it 300 points?
(Will the members be able to gift everything to Chief Kang?)
How would we beat a pro?
- He's a pro. - In a game of darts...
Even pros might make mistakes under pressure.
(Hoping)
- Under pressure. - So you must...
collect as many darts as possible through missions.
(The more darts the members collect, the better their chances are.)
- That gives us more chances. - With more darts.
The pro will throw only three darts per round,
while you can throw as many darts as you've earned...
through the missions.
- We get more chances. - I'll try hard today.
(By collecting darts)
We should give him the Onnuri gift certificates.
(What's the first mission to collect the darts?)
The Onnuri gift certificates are the best.
This doesn't look like a hanging game.
(A pull-up bar over a vinyl-covered floor)
It's too hard to hang from the pull-up bar.
- There are balloons. - We have balloons.
(Black balloons piled high)
I think we will have to throw these balloons over the bar...
for the other side to catch.
- I don't think I can do it. - The first mission...
for earning darts is...
Landmine Water Balloons.
- Landmine? - We throw them over.
When two members catch the water balloons...
thrown over the bar using baskets held over their heads,
one dart will be added for each catch.
We will give you a total of 20 balloons,
but hidden among those 20 are five colored water balloons.
- Oh, no. - Come on!
If a colored water balloon bursts while you try to catch it,
all the darts you've earned so far will vanish.
- I see. - Oh, no!
(Beginning to whine)
There's no advantage for us.
- This is too much. - It's too harsh.
Before throwing the next balloon,
you may discuss whether to continue the mission...
or stop there...
and bank the darts...
- you have earned. - We can do that.
- It's our choice. - We can stop and lock it in.
(Members can choose whether to stop with decent success or go for more.)
We have to decide...
- whether to stop or push forward. - Yes.
- Getting 15 darts is enough. - By the way, even the thrower...
- can't tell the colored ones? - No.
They deliberately used black balloons.
(A big loss if a colored water balloon pops...)
Now, please choose the two people to catch the water balloons.
(after such a good collection)
(Selecting the 2 balloon receivers for Round 1)
- We should throw them well. - We should.
- And we should catch carefully. - We can't stand still.
(The balloon receivers must be good at controlling the basket.)
- We should catch them like this. - Right. Smoothly.
Jong Kook is good at stuff like this.
- I'm good. - With Jong Kook,
(Confident)
Ye Eun should try it.
(Me?)
I'm not good.
I'm too weak to do this.
- Ye Eun is... - You're trying to be funny.
- Is this a joke? - Ye Eun is extraordinary.
(Recommending with a clear goal)
- Jae Seok. - I'll throw the balloons.
(Everyone can throw except for the 2 receivers.)
- And Seok Jin should do it. - Not me.
Let's just give it a try first.
(Director Kang Chan Hee's gift task force is on the move.)
Okay.
You're the best.
Ye Eun and Ji Hyo.
(Receivers)
- Ye Eun and Ji Hyo. - Ye Eun and Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo and Ye Eun are the receivers of Round 1.)
- They will do well. - Ye Eun and Ji Hyo.
Rather than using a towel...
(Checking the balloons)
Hang on.
I can't see inside the balloons.
I can't tell if this is colored or not.
(Colored water balloon)
(Weighing it in hand?)
(Unable to differentiate them by appearance or weight)
This is pretty heavy.
- Hey. - Throw them carefully.
Ye Eun, I'll take the back.
(The Ji Song Sisters are ready.)
Let's begin Round One. Ready.
- Start. - Let's go.
Let's do this.
(Round 1 begins.)
Be careful.
(They must catch the balloons to win Chan Hee his gifts!)
Go.
(Will they be able to catch them without popping?)
There you go.
- Go. - There you go.
(Burst!)
- Oh, no. - My goodness.
- There you go. - Oh, no.
- Keep it over your head! - What's with them?
(Belatedly getting into position)
- Over your head. - Hey!
- What are you guys doing? - Keep it over your head.
(Goodness)
- You can't do it like this. - Okay.
Ji Hyo, you should track the balloon and move accordingly.
Keep it above your head.
(Nagging at them nonstop as soon as the game starts)
Try harder!
And...
when the balloon comes down, lower your bodies like this.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
(Teaching them in person)
- That's it. - Good!
(Balloons remaining: 19)
This is clear water!
Here I go.
(Seok Sam is the next thrower.)
It shouldn't be the colored one.
- Here I go. - It shouldn't be the colored one.
(Will the relentless nagging work?)
- Good. - Here I go.
- That's good. - It shouldn't be the colored one.
(Splashing)
Okay. It's water.
- It's a relief. - It's water.
(The content of every balloon thrown is being revealed.)
It's water.
(Wide awake)
(The two still haven't gotten the hang of it.)
Go, Ji Ye Eun!
(Balloons remaining: 18)
Go, Song Ji Hyo!
(This time, the Hobbit throws the balloon.)
- You must cushion the impact. - One, two...
All right. It's been clear water.
(There you go!)
Ye Eun, stand straight up.
(What about this time?)
All right. It's been clear water.
There you go.
(Burst!)
(It's a colored water balloon.)
Okay. Oh, dear.
(Again, they absorbed the water with their bodies.)
You should've received it.
(Blaming each other)
You should throw it properly!
You failed to catch it.
(Angry)
You hobbit!
- Hobbit? - Throw better, you hobbit!
- You should've thrown it better. - Seriously.
(The colored water balloon burst,)
(but they have no darts to lose.)
- I mean... - Ye Eun, here we go.
- Let's do this. - Go, team.
(Trying again with renewed determination)
- Go, team. - Come on. Let's do better.
Aim better this time.
(Balloons remaining: 17)
Okay, here goes.
(Will the Ji Song Sisters catch it this time?)
No, don't bend your knees.
- I'm trying to level our height. - I see.
- All right. Stay sharp. - Looking good.
(He throws it.)
(The right direction)
(Burst!)
(Eyes squeezed shut)
Looking good.
- Don't close your eyes! - Seriously?
Why are you closing your eyes and not keeping them on the balloon?
Grandpa, can't you see the basket?
You should keep your eyes on the balloon!
(The Aqua Duo are frustrated with each other.)
Why would you close your eyes?
- Keep your eyes on it. - Why would you close your eyes?
- This is fun, right? - She called him Grandpa.
(Awful skills, but guaranteed entertainment)
- Let's keep going. - This is fun.
Let's pick up the speed. Get ready.
I'll be the one to throw now.
- These need to burst. - I'll do that.
- Who's up next? - It's Haha.
(The Hobbit's walk looks questioningly confident.)
- Here. - Go ahead.
- Let's catch it. - Keep your eyes on it.
(He's acting suspicious.)
- Keep holding it up. - One...
- Two... - More.
- Here. - Keep your eyes on it.
- Keep holding it up. - One, two...
Put it in the basket for them.
(Flying away)
Don't close your eyes!
- Don't close your eyes! - Done.
(Burst!)
(What the...)
- Hey! - Hey! Are you kidding me?
(Throwing down)
Throw it better, I'm warning you!
It's not that. He actually threw it well.
(The Eight-Foot Tall Ghost is off to scold the Hobbit.)
- Ye Eun. - It wasn't bad.
Ye Eun, get back here.
(Summoned back as soon as she sets off)
You! Get over here.
Hold it.
Don't bend your knees before the balloon starts dropping.
(Balloon)
- Don't bend them. - Why are you all ganging up on me?
(The teamwork has burst along with the balloon.)
Do better, will you? We need to get at least one.
- Here. Catch. - The earlier one was too short.
(Trying again)
- Only bend slightly. - This will work.
- They've got this one. - Goodness.
(Plopping)
(No hope whatsoever)
- Should it burst like that? - Tell me about it.
People will think we're picking on you.
- Hey. - Seriously...
- Can't we switch it up? - Hey.
- This isn't so bad. - Switch it up for me.
Exactly. Switch places with them.
(This round is a losing game.)
- How could you not even catch one? - Let's discuss this.
(Switching players)
I think they'll be easy to catch.
(Balloon)
As the balloon comes closer, retreat like so.
That's it. Welcome the balloon into the basket.
(Why can't you do it?)
- Welcome it in. - Why didn't you do that?
If you think you can do better, go ahead.
- We will. We'll show you. - Unbelievable.
- Okay. Se Chan, go ahead. - I'll be the catcher.
(Like that, Round 2's receivers have been decided.)
I should do this. I'll get it done.
(Ssaebssaeb knows how it works,)
Okay.
(and Muscle is serious when it comes to ball games.)
Jong Kook, smooth is the way to go.
(Setting out with determination for Chief Kang)
We're done for if another colored water balloon bursts.
- Let's do this. - Go, team!
Why don't we hold it down here?
- How about we hold it like this? - Sure. Jong Kook, wait.
(Under the basket)
- Let's swing the basket like this. - Or...
(The swing strategy)
- The legs too, but... - You must hold it above your head.
(Writer)
- What? - Above your head.
- Catch it above your head. - You must hold it above your head.
(They must receive the balloon from above their heads.)
- Above our heads? - Above our heads?
Above them?
(Then)
- Down. - Here. You and me...
- Okay. One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Down. - That's it.
(The squat strategy)
We need to throw them well.
- One, two, three. - Stay behind the white line.
- You can't cross the line. - What?
Seriously? What's with all the rules?
- That's a lot. - Unbelievable.
(Defamation)
It's like you don't want to give Chan Hee any gifts.
(Why you...)
Get ready for Round Two.
(They must make up for it this time to get closer to Chan Hee's gift!)
- Go, team! - Get ready.
- Okay! - Let's do better this time.
(Round 2 begins.)
- Let's do this. - Throw them well.
(Jae Seok throws the balloon.)
- Oh, no. - He threw it hard.
(Lips pursed tight)
Looking good.
- Looking good. - He threw it hard.
(Safely in the basket!)
- Did we get it? - Okay, you got it.
- Hold on. - Okay, you got it.
(Ssaeb-Kook received the first balloon safely!)
Hold on. What now?
(Excited)
- Over there. - Place it in that basket.
- Wasn't that good? - Jae Seok, that was perfect.
- Put it over there. - That was good. Keep it that way.
(Collected darts)
That's how you throw it.
(Proudly)
- While catching it... - Keep looking at it.
Like this. Hold it up like so.
(Keep your eyes on it until the end.)
When the balloon comes,
(Absorb the shock by squatting.)
lower the basket while bending your knees.
- Got it. - Please let this work.
(Grandpa Jee is next to throw.)
- Please. Just like this. - Let's do this.
(The balloon is thrown!)
- Where is it? - Not there.
(Will they be able to catch this one too?)
Where is it?
(A full squat)
(They caught another one!)
- Yes! - Nice.
(They've got the hang of it by squatting.)
(Collected darts)
- No way. - We're so good.
(They already earned 2 darts!)
All right. Ji Hyo, you already look scared.
(The next thrower is Ji Hyo.)
- It's not that. - Choose one for me.
(Pitcher Song has a highly unpredictable aim.)
Try to loosen up a bit.
Ji Hyo, check the balloon again.
It should seem like these two.
(Anxious)
How's the balloon?
- Choose one for me. - It seems fine.
I think that's going to burst.
(For some reason)
(Pitcher Song is hard to trust.)
I don't think she'll throw it properly.
- She doesn't have enough strength. - But...
- Just go for it. - This one?
(Ji Hyo, who seems shaky, throws the balloon hard!)
(Soaring)
I have a bad feeling about this. It's too high!
(The balloon shoots straight up.)
It's too high!
(They managed to save it!)
- Did we get it? - Yes.
(Nerve-racking)
- I want to try. - I can't believe that didn't burst.
(Collected darts)
You've gotten three so far.
(Ssaeb-Kook caught 3 in a row!)
Nice job.
Hold on a second. Are we going to keep going?
- Hold on. - Just keep going.
(If a colored water balloon bursts, the darts are reset!)
We're fine as long as we don't pop any colored water balloons.
Two...
(It's high!)
(Burst!)
(Ssaeb-Kook lets a balloon burst for the first time.)
(Relieved)
It's only water.
- That didn't matter. - Okay, that's fine.
It's only water. We're safe.
(The dart count stays the same, as it wasn't a colored water balloon.)
- I'll go next. - Okay.
That didn't matter.
(The next pitcher is Ddochi.)
I want to try.
I have a feeling this will burst.
- Ye Eun. - Just don't let it be colored.
- Anything but colored water. - Please.
Anything but colored water.
- Anything but colored water. - Bend your knees.
(She sends the balloon soaring with a weak cry.)
(They caught it!)
- We did it. - Nice.
(Sticky Hands catches everything.)
- Nice. - Great.
You guys are great at this.
(Already collected 4 darts)
- Nice. - Keep your eyes on it.
How are they this good?
(Amazed)
We're doing great.
(Trying for the 5th dart in a row)
I know I can do this.
How many do you want us to get?
- We should keep going. - We already got a lot.
- Why don't we just get 5? - Yes, 5.
- What should we do? - Doesn't...
the colored water balloon reset things for us?
- How about 5? - Yes, 5.
(They should secure the 4 darts.)
I think five is the right amount.
- We'll end it with this one. - How many do we have?
(Let's try another balloon.)
We have four.
(The Tiger Moths have already tasted victory.)
Make sure to catch this.
- We'll push through. - Let's get this one for now.
- Is this the last one? - We'll push through.
If it's a colored water balloon, that'll hit the reset button.
(Nervous)
It won't matter.
(What's the result of not stopping for the 5th time?)
It won't matter if it's water!
- Nice. - We got it.
(Success!)
It won't matter if it's water!
(Heave-ho!)
- Nice. - We got it.
That's 16 years in a nutshell.
(The 16-year broken record has appeared.)
- Should we stop here? - Yes, let's stop here.
(If they stop now, they'll secure 5 darts!)
- Five? - How about one more?
- No, let's stop. - Okay, one more.
(Another one again?)
- Should we stop? - Let's stop.
- What if that one pops? - No, don't.
(Mr. Jee takes a risk knowing that...)
- Don't. - That could pop.
(a colored water balloon will reset everything.)
- Chan Hee. - Should we stop?
Go or stop? What should it be?
- Chan Hee, what do you say? - Go?
(What's Chief Kang's call?)
Chan Hee, should we throw one more?
- Go for it. - He greenlit it.
- Chan Hee gave us the go-ahead. - He allowed it.
(Getting ready after hearing Cool Guy Chan Hee...)
- But... - Let's do this.
(telling them to go for it)
- Should we try one more? - Let's do it.
- So I'm getting a feeling. - Sure.
This feels cold to the touch.
- Okay. - Wouldn't that be tap water?
- That's it. - Go for it.
(A reason he pulled out of thin air)
(What's the outcome of them taking a chance?)
You threw it too hard.
(They caught it!)
(Received the 6th balloon)
That's 16 years in a nutshell.
Sixteen years, people.
(This is what you call 16 years!)
No way, we got it.
- All right. - We're unstoppable.
(They're all moved by the unpopped balloons.)
Gosh, we're so good at this.
We're so good at this.
What can we do when we're so good at this?
(Reading the director's face)
- No more. - We should stop now.
Stop?
It's time to stop.
(Getting scared after securing 6 darts)
- Stop. - We should stop.
- More? - Do we carry on?
Chan Hee, should we stop?
(What's the Cool Guy's call?)
- Stop. - Stopping is the wise choice.
(Enough.)
- Stop. - Yes, stop.
(Chief Kang knows how far the members' luck can take them.)
- How many did we get? - Six.
- Nice. - We got six.
(Stopped after safely securing 6 darts)
You caught six balloons.
- Yes, we got a lot. - Great job.
You'll receive six darts.
(Number of darts: 6)
- Okay! - Okay!
(They head to the next location feeling good about themselves.)
- We got six for now. - Nice.
- We caught a lot of balloons. - We start off with six.
(Satisfied)
- Six is a lot. - That'll make things easy for us.
Six is a lot.
- Yes, it's a lot. - I can't believe it.
Chan Hee seemed really happy with us.
- Exactly. Six darts give us... - Right.
(Thankfully, the members have something to show the director.)
- a fighting chance. - Yes, that's enough.
By the way, we're up against a professional dart player.
(The opponent)
That's why we need as many darts...
- as we can get. - The dart player...
- could get five darts too. - Exactly.
(The safe move is to secure as many darts as possible.)
- Then we'll need... - About 20 of them.
He finished second in an international tournament.
- Really? - I knew it.
That means he hits the bullseye most of the time.
Seok Sam used to hit up dart bars back in the day.
- Really? - I wasn't going to say anything,
(Team Running Man's secret weapon: A dart bar regular)
but I used to just play darts for fun.
As you know, Yong Man, Soo Yong,
and I aren't drinkers.
Did they even have dart bars back in your day?
- So... - Of course.
Didn't you just play with a makeshift target?
Didn't you play with a target you drew on a tree?
(These little...)
Wasn't there a woman with an apple on her head?
- Like William Tell? - Yes.
- Wasn't he an archer? - Did you say William Tell?
Do you think I'm that old?
(From the darts' founding father to a legendary hunter)
- Hold on. - William Tell?
- Did I spend time in England? - William Tell.
Didn't you throw sticks that you sharpened yourself?
- I guess I could have. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Wasn't it a dagger?
It could've been a dagger.
(Playing along)
Seok Jin is letting all the jokes land today.
(What's going on?)
- He's in great form today. - Yes, he's feeling great.
(He's in the best mood to play along.)
- I love it. - He isn't even getting angry.
It's fine. Besides, it's a great day today.
- Exactly. But why? - Why is it a great day?
- It just is. - The stock market took a dip.
Even if it drops, now...
- I just let it go. - Really?
Yes, I just let it go.
(Jee Seok Sam is now immune to being in the red.)
Of course. Now...
- I'm not going to sell them. - Exactly.
There was a time...
when the stock market was all we talked about.
I know. Things were crazy.
(Being in the green was short and sweet.)
- We were all happy. - Everyone was in a good mood.
My heart broke over the stock market,
- but even that scabbed over. - It went beyond that.
- Of course. - It hurt so much...
- that the wound healed over. - I see.
Those who don't invest in the stock market...
might be the real winners after all.
- Right. - Of course.
(Glancing)
But...
- I'm holding out. - Ye Eun, tell them.
- It's good if you make money. - Of course.
She's having a hard time too.
Ye Eun, do you invest in stocks too?
- She got into it during this run. - I gave it a try.
I'm down 47 percent.
Oh, dear.
(Ddochi is at the summit.)
- Ye Eun... - She only bought blue-chip stocks.
Didn't you get into it against our advice?
(Being hateful)
- You tried to stop me. - We told you to stay away.
(Bitter)
But I dreamed of hitting it big too.
- Well, everyone was making money. - Everyone around her...
(A textbook retail investor)
was talking about the stock market.
(Everyone would've downloaded the stock app back then.)
- She got swayed... - How could you not, right?
by all the talk.
- Of course. Besides, - That's right.
the FOMO is real.
- You're afraid you're missing out. - That's right.
I doubt many of them know what FOMO is.
I understood the gist of it.
(Confessing)
- Really? FOMO? - Which is what?
You're afraid you'll miss out on something.
- Nice. - Not bad.
(Impressed)
I'm the living embodiment of FOMO.
(Seok Sam is suddenly upset.)
- You can't take it. - I lose sleep over it.
I'm sorry about this, but...
- What is it? - Aren't we giving Chan Hee gifts?
- We should be talking about that. - Hold on.
You've been talking about something else this whole time.
- How far do we need to take this? - Give him stocks, then.
You could've just told us to stop, you punk.
- Why are you raising your voice? - There's no need to get angry.
(His condition has turned red.)
That's not it.
- We were all talking. - There's no need for that.
Why are you only telling me...
- to stop? - Hold on.
- He's like a kid. - Unbelievable.
(Where did they land with Seok Jin, who's like the stock market itself?)
What on earth is this?
Wait, what's this?
- Cones were set up everywhere. - Right.
(A cone-lined path stretching from the inside out)
I bet it's a relay.
(What are we doing here?)
- What's that? - What do they have planned?
In this next game, you'll play to win darts and lunch.
- We need to do this right. - We have to do well on this one.
- This is Draw at Full Speed. - We have to nail this.
- At full speed? - At full speed?
- Four of you must compete. - Okay.
Three of you will get the answer, then go to your starting positions.
The first participant must then run as they start to draw.
The sketchbook is passed to the next runner like a baton.
The fourth person must guess the answer from the drawing.
(Correct)
- That's hard. - How do we do that?
- The time limit is 30 seconds. - What?
- That's too short. - All three runners must draw.
- Jong Kook's good at drawing. - You can't use numbers or letters.
(No letters or numbers allowed.)
My gosh...
(Everything has to be conveyed through drawings.)
- While we run? - While we run?
- That's tough. - What are the categories?
- They're proverbs. Yes. - Proverbs?
- Not bad. - Proverbs are hard.
(Proverb genius)
- Shouldn't Ye Eun run? - She should.
- Ye Eun should run. - For entertainment.
- She can draw well too. - Yes.
(Empty Head Ji, her only forte is proverbs and drawings.)
- I can draw. - Yes.
- There are seven questions. - Okay.
- Seven questions. - The number of side dishes...
are also seven, and each time you fail...
(Every time they get it wrong, one of the side dishes will be removed.)
- That's harsh. - That's not fair.
- You lose what you like most. - I'm hurt.
That means you just want to start a fight.
- Don't use food against us. - Food...
(Mr. Free Meals is mad.)
I'll show you the full menu.
(7 side dishes are coming.)
Look!
- That's a feast. - We must try hard.
(Passionate)
- Let's get everything right. - Gosh.
(1. Spicy stir-fried pork, 2. Steak with herbs)
- What the... - That's insane.
(4. Seaweed soup, 6. Young radish mulkimchi, seasoned perilla leaves)
- I can't lose any. - It's too much.
- Japchae? - Just seaweed soup and rice...
(7. Orange salad, acorn jelly)
- is delicious enough. - We need seasoned perilla leaves.
(From appetizing Korean side dishes...)
- Spicy stir-fried pork. - My favorites...
(to delicious and nutritious meat dishes)
- are all here. - The steak.
- Steak with herbs. - We just need the pork.
- No, the steak. - It looks so good.
(These 7 dishes are the members' favorites.)
Don't they all look great?
- We just need the spicy pork. - The pork.
- A man's favorite! - Spicy pork!
(Spicy stir-fried pork sent their enthusiasm through the roof.)
We just need the spicy pork.
- The menu... - Pork is all we need.
- Spicy pork! - Just one.
- The thing is, - Pork is all we need.
you lose them in numerical order.
- Shoot. - That's not fair.
- We should decide. - Let us choose what to lose.
(1. Spicy stir-fried pork, 2. Steak with herbs)
- Shall we fight? - Wait.
Numerical order is too cruel.
That's not fair. Let us pick one by one.
(Checking the temperature)
Jong Kook, it's warm. We must play now.
- Let's play. - The food is warm.
(They'll quickly start the challenge before the food gets cold.)
Due to stamina issues,
- the two groups will take turns. - Okay.
Jong Kook and Haha are the two resident artists.
- You each pick a team to lead. - That's fair.
I'll take these landmines.
(Serious)
- "Landmines?" - We survived with wit.
(The landmines are offended.)
- Was that too mean? - You do that.
- Jae Seok can guess. - Yes.
(Jae Seok has gotten so much better at drawing.)
- His drawing got much better. - I did.
(Seal, Bongeun Temple, horse, Ji Ye Eun)
I improved over the years.
(And this is what his "improved" drawing looks like.)
Despite the improvement, no one can decipher his art.
I'll guess the answer.
- You know many proverbs. - I do. I lived those times.
- That's right. - Yes.
We have to run, right?
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Haha, and Se Chan go first.)
How do you draw as you run?
You should go first, then.
- Me? - Go first and set the tone.
(Haha, you go first and set the tone.)
No, I'll draw last and Jae Seok...
(I'll draw last.)
No. You must start it off,
- so we don't mess up. - He should provide the plan.
(The landmines are not confident enough to go first.)
- That's only right. - He should go last.
- I know that. - Sketch it out for us.
- I know that! - He knows that!
- Gosh, seriously... - Jae Seok focuses...
on different points.
Listen up, Hobbit.
Do as we say. How dare a hobbit...
Why are you so...
- Excuse me. - You must provide the outline.
- I can... - I get that.
(Raising his hand)
Sir, we're filming. Get out of the way.
The last runner...
That must be you.
- I'll go last. - I'll decide for you.
- I'm the guesser. - We're filming.
(Rejecting)
- Oh, you're filming? - Yes.
Listen, I will...
(Squeezing in)
- We can't draw. - Mister.
- I'm guessing the answer! - I mean...
- They'll draw a mess. - Sorting out...
There's no time. You have five seconds to say.
- Five... - Start.
- Five, four, - He'll clean up.
- three, two, - He'll clean up the mess.
(A clear explanation)
- one. - I said it in five seconds.
You'll mess up,
- and he'll clean up. - We won't mess up.
(Persuaded)
- You won't? - No.
- How about... - Haha, you go last.
- I should go last. - Okay, you go last.
- Have a go. - You go last.
(They reluctantly accept CEO Ha's suggestion.)
You're so darn stubborn.
- You go first. - Oh, good idea.
- Plan Left-right. - I'll go first.
Plan Left-right. Halve the proverb...
- It's darker... - It's darker under the lamp.
(On the left, on the right)
- Left and right. - Okay, got it.
(They're seriously plotting a left-right strategy.)
You go second.
(Order for Round 1: Jae Seok, Se Chan, Haha, Seok Jin)
I'm done for. I can't draw.
I'm nervous. Where's the track? Where do I run to?
Jae Seok will come to me?
Can this be done in 30 seconds?
(They have 30 seconds!)
It's really hard.
(The first proverb: To go on market day.)
Good luck, Jae Seok. We're a team.
(To go on market day)
How do you draw this?
(Unsure)
This... This is too difficult.
(It's hard to describe.)
(The others also read the proverb.)
- I see. - This is too hard.
(To go on market day)
- Ready. - Jae Seok, we're a team.
Get set, go.
You have 30 seconds.
Go.
(He starts drawing as soon as he sets off.)
(He draws a bit, then runs at full speed.)
You can't draw much.
(He hands it to Se Chan, the 2nd player.)
What's this? Oh, okay.
Gosh, this is hard.
(He drew a person and a road!)
Hey. Do something with that.
(He described "to go.")
Plan Left-right. Halve it.
(They'd agreed on a plan to split the drawing.)
- It's darker... - It's darker under the lamp.
- Halve it. - Paper is lighter...
(Se Chan has to draw the second half!)
- when carried together. - Okay.
Se Chan, you just run.
Just run! Run!
(He's drawing something.)
- Please! - Just run!
(He keeps drawing until the end.)
Go!
- It's so hard. - Gosh.
- What the heck is this? - It's impossible.
- It's hard. - What the heck is this?
- It's impossible. - He said "what the heck."
(To go on market day)
You can't draw as you run.
Run faster!
- He'll clean up the mess. - He'll clean up the mess.
(Too little time to clean up the mess)
- Two, one! - Run faster.
- Run! - Do you know the answer?
(He barely made it in time.)
Take a look, Seok Jin. Let's look at it together.
(Seok Sam, who will guess the answer, receives the drawing.)
- What is it? - Let's see.
It's too difficult.
- It's a really easy proverb. - What is this?
It's hard to describe.
(A drawing that makes no sense)
- What... - How are you to...
Didn't we mention this one?
(Sighing)
- Kicking... - This proverb...
- I drew the most. - I think it's about kicking.
(The drawing is so bad that it's not easy to decipher.)
This is...
No.
Is he peeing or kicking something?
I drew the most and best.
What part did you draw?
(Painter Yu's drawing is the only one he can understand.)
- The left part. - Is it about urinating?
Pee?
- It looks like someone's urinating. - The square...
- What's the answer? - Seok Jin.
(Will Seok Jin be able to figure out the proverb?)
- There aren't that many proverbs. - Five,
- four, three, - Three...
two,
- one. - I don't know.
Peeing on frozen feet?
- Incorrect. - What is it?
To go on market day.
(Correct answer)
- It's impossible to draw. - He's going.
- How can you tell? - He's on the way.
- It was a hard one. - The second part...
- This was... - That wasn't easy. It was hard.
You got the first question wrong, so you lose the spicy pork.
- Take the salad. - No, it's the pork.
(No)
- You lose the pork. - Hey.
- They'll take the pork. - No!
(Telling tales)
- Come on. - That's not fair.
(What?)
- Spicy pork is a man's meal. - Come on.
You're forcing us to play darts.
At least let us choose what we eat.
That's not right. Spicy pork is a man's meal.
(Kook wants to keep spicy stir-fried pork, which is his favorite.)
(Bye)
- No! - Take the salad.
(The spicy stir-fried pork is out.)
Can't they take the salad?
If they take the spicy pork...
Shall Ye Eun and I have a go?
- Who goes first? - First...
(They enter Round 2, curious over losing the spicy stir-fried pork.)
- I'll go first. - Shall I go second?
- You're on our team? - It's tough.
This game...
(Order for Round 2: Jong Kook, Ye Eun, Ji Hyo, Jae Seok)
Why is it... The track is this long?
- I'll walk fast at first. - Ye Eun.
(In the beginning)
Draw while walking fast...
(He's burning with determination after losing the stir-fried pork.)
Ye Eun, read the proverb first.
Balance the paper on my shirt.
Jong Kook is a machine when it comes to playing games.
He is. He treats it like it's an international competition.
Let's do this. Let's win Chan Hee some presents.
(With Jong Kook in this round, they have a better chance of winning.)
- Yes, let's win him something. - Good luck.
Give me a piece of paper.
(The 1st player checks the question.)
Okay.
(Even in a tiger's den, you can survive with your wits.)
The first runner must draw the most.
Ready.
(Jae Seok will guess the answer.)
Good luck!
(Keywords: Tiger, wit)
- Get set. - In the 80s...
(Even in a tiger's den, you can survive with your wits.)
Okay...
Hurry up.
- There's no time. - Hurry up.
(He's sketching while walking fast.)
Run! You have to run!
Now run!
(Running at full speed)
- Run! - He's running.
He finished his drawing.
(Painter Kook drew a perfect tiger!)
(He runs while shouting loudly.)
Where are you?
- Did he draw everything? - Was he always this silly?
- Not before. - He wasn't.
- He changed. - He's weird.
(He arrives chanting a spell.)
This is where you start?
- You drew something? A tiger. - I drew a tiger.
(He hands it to Ye Eun, the 2nd player.)
- A tiger. - Go.
- Draw something about being alert. - Being alert.
(Panting)
Describe someone staying alert, and they'll get it!
Being alert!
(She drew "being alert" perfectly!)
It's easy. Ye Eun, being alert.
(Painter Ji draws a person as well.)
Run!
- Ji Hyo, run! - Just run!
- Get over here! - Ten seconds to go!
(She hands it to Ji Hyo when they have 10 seconds left.)
- Ji Hyo, run! - Just run!
(If she can't make it in time, they'll fail!)
- Just run! - Get in on time!
- Four, three, two, - Run!
(Adding the finishing touch,)
- one. - She made it.
(she made it just in time.)
Okay.
- It's done? - Let's see.
(Even in a tiger's den, you can survive with your wits.)
I got it.
Hang on, a tiger...
It's really easy!
(He immediately recognizes the high-quality tiger.)
It's easy!
What's the answer?
Even if you meet a tiger, stay alert and you survive.
- That's it. - Correct.
(Jae Seok got it right.)
Okay!
Even in a tiger's den...
(Feeling proud)
- I drew this part! - Staying alert.
- Good job. - It worked.
(Ye Eun's drawing skills could make her the next ace!)
- This was crucial. - I drew it.
- Well done. - It's about staying alert.
- This part helped. - Good for you.
- Great job. - I did well, right?
(They kept 6 side dishes and earned 1 dart.)
- Good job. - That's it.
Let's do this!
- Hey, Jong Kook! - What?
(Keeping the momentum going, Seok Sam steps up.)
Whatever the first half of the proverb will be,
(1st player)
I'll draw that on the left so you can draw the rest.
(Jong Kook, the 2nd player)
I'll do that.
If it's about holding a piece of paper, I'll draw paper!
- Okay. - If it's about maggots...
(Chuckling)
stopping you from making doenjang, I'll draw maggots.
- Okay? - I'll draw the clay pot.
Seok Jin. You need to run, remember?
(Calm down.)
- Okay. - You have to run.
Okay?
If it's about a quiet cat jumping onto a stove,
(Seok Sam is highly motivated.)
I'll draw a quiet cat.
- Seok Jin. - If it's about stringing pearls,
(He shouts his resolve into the air.)
I'll draw pearls while you draw the string.
He keeps talking when he's out of earshot.
I'll show you what I can do at full speed.
(Order for Round 3: Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Se Chan, Jae Seok)
I'm guessing it, right?
Halve the proverb!
(The 1st runner reads the answer.)
Ready.
Get set.
(Start)
Run!
He looks his age from behind.
(The old artist looks great for his age from the front.)
Shoot. Where do I go? Where is it?
It's this far away? This is bad.
(He's lost because his sense of direction isn't what it used to be.)
You can't hide your age. It shows.
It shows in what you do.
(Stay strong, Seok Sam.)
You must run faster. You're too slow.
(Rushing)
Darn it.
How do you depict this?
- What did you draw? What's this? - How many seconds?
This is bad. I can't do it.
(The great painter is trying to fix it quickly.)
Get over here. Run!
You need to run!
- Fifteen seconds! - You can do it!
- There's no time! - What is this, Seok Jin?
(He's determined to finish drawing the next keyword.)
- Run! - Run!
- It's so tough. - Run.
(Ssaebssaeb receives the drawing and starts running.)
- Just run! - He's coming.
- Run! - You can get it.
- Run! - How...
(He barely drew a line...)
How much time do we have?
- It's easy! - We can guess it.
(and made it.)
- You did it. - I'm on time.
What is it?
(Jae Seok checks the drawing.)
- What's this? - It's easy!
The two parts are connected.
What is this?
(Seok Sam and Painter Kook's drawings are connected by an arrow.)
- What's this? - What did they draw?
Okay. You can guess this.
What is this?
(Hunched back)
Goodness.
- Goodness. - You can't do that.
(Painter Kook is moving around next to him.)
What did I do?
I'm just tired from all the running.
Goodness, a cane...
What's the answer?
- Okay! - He got it.
There's a three. One, two, three.
(3 fingers Seok Sam drew)
Think carefully.
(Will he figure out Seok Sam's drawing...)
Please.
Please, let us get it right.
(and keep the only meat dish that is left...)
Please!
- He'll get it. - Okay!
(and get a dart?)
He got it.
Habits formed at 3 last until you're 80.
Yes!
(Correct)
Good!
(Jae Seok got it right again.)
You should have drawn a baby here!
- Drawing a baby isn't easy. - Three.
(Fingers)
- Why can't you draw a baby? - You counted the three.
This was supposed to be three.
(He drew "3 years old" with 3 giant fingers.)
- You could have drawn a baby. - A baby...
- There's a three. - This is a baby.
(And Jae Seok figured it out.)
- Good job. We got it right. - Nice.
(The giant fingers were the biggest hint.)
- We got it right. - Very nice.
This was difficult.
It was difficult.
(They get extra darts.)
- You get these. - Okay.
Okay, then...
- Ji Hyo, Ye Eun, - Haha?
(Order for Round 4: Ye Eun, Ji Hyo, Haha)
- and Haha. - Haha.
- I'll go first. - Jong Kook could guess the answer.
(Order for Round 4: Ye Eun, Ji Hyo, Haha, Jong Kook)
- Jong Kook can guess it. - I'll run.
Will you run?
I'll be the last runner.
Take your time to draw.
You have to run quickly, Haha!
(Looking confident)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Ye Eun checks the proverb.)
- It fits. - Ye Eun...
- How do I draw this? - She's the genius at drawing.
(Not knowing what to do)
- Ready... - How should I draw this?
(When your cousin buys land, your stomach hurts.)
You can do it.
- Draw it in your head. - Think it through.
- Divide it in half. - Make it simple.
(There are many keywords this time.)
Divide the paper in half and draw the left side,
- then go to the right side. - Right. Make it simple.
You can split it into two parts, right?
Draw in the first four steps then start running!
(Will Ye Eun, the first player, be able to draw it well?)
- You can do it! - Get ready.
- Take five seconds. - You have to run, Ye Eun.
(Start)
You have to run.
You have to run, Ye Eun.
(Running)
(Ye Eun just starts running as she was told.)
- Walk four steps! - You have to run.
Walk and then.... She's just...
It won't work if she runs like that.
(She seems to be too focused on running to draw anything.)
- Can she draw anything like that? - It's over.
Why aren't you drawing?
She's not drawing!
You have to draw something.
- She... - You have to draw something.
She really runs like this.
Why aren't you drawing?
(The Eight-Foot-Tall Giant really runs like one in "Attack on Titan.")
She's not drawing!
How did it go?
(She hands it over to Ji Hyo.)
(When your cousin buys land, your stomach hurts.)
(She managed to draw a lot!)
(Cousin, land, pear)
(When your cousin buys land, your stomach hurts.)
Run!
(She adds a checkerboard grid detail on the land.)
You have ten seconds left.
Just run!
(Haha, the 3rd runner starts running with 10 seconds left.)
I said, run!
- Ten... - There are only ten seconds left.
Just run!
(Nervous)
- I said run! - Hurry!
- Just run! - Five,
(Painter Ha, who was confident, adds the finishing touch.)
- Five. - four,
- Just run. - three, two,
- one. - Just run.
(He barely made it.)
Good.
Goodness.
There's a finger.
(Haha's drawing)
They drew a finger.
- Come to the back. - A finger.
(Painter Ha added fingers.)
- Come to the back. - There's a finger.
Come to the back.
- There's a finger. - I drew this as well.
(Haha drew this one too.)
I was telling him what I drew.
- What is this? - Come to the back.
(So many details are added to Ye Eun's sketch.)
You shouldn't tell him.
- What is this? - You drew a finger.
- Here's a person. Ye Eun drew this. - Yes.
(He's looking over the drawing carefully.)
This is a person,
and you drew a board.
Ye Eun drew this.
This is a person, and you drew a board.
What was it about "finding Mr. Kim?"
(Whispering)
- A board. - What?
- "Finding Mr. Kim in Seoul." - Right.
- Is that correct? - Yes.
(While Ssaebssaeb is going down the wrong track...)
You shouldn't tell him.
It's like a checkerboard.
- It looks tasty. - No.
- No. You shouldn't tell him. - You shouldn't tell him.
What is this? Is this bread?
That's...
- Is this bread? Bread. - Jong Kook!
(Bread)
- He noticed it. - Why did you draw bread?
- Hold on. What... - Why did you draw bread?
Bread...
(Surprised)
- Five, - Why did you draw bread?
- four, - Why did you draw bread?
- three, two... - Why did you draw bread?
Bread?
(Bread threw everything into chaos.)
- Five, four, - Hold on.
- three, two, - Why did you draw bread?
- one. - What is this?
Why did you draw bread?
(Time is up.)
- What is this? - You failed.
- "When your cousin buys land," - That's correct.
(Correct answer)
"your stomach hurts."
Did you think the land was bread?
- Bread... - Bread...
(Oh, no)
- Bread... - You thought the land was bread?
- Seriously... - You idiot!
(Slamming)
- Still... - Why would your stomach hurt...
- when your cousin buys bread? - Why is the bread...
It's not "bread..."
- Why would he buy bread? - The proverb...
(Is he hungry? Or is he just that dumb?)
- Why would he buy bread? - What is he doing?
Did the cousin buy bread?
(He can't believe it.)
Why would there be bread in a proverb?
That's foreign food. A rice cake would've been understandable.
That person would be really horrible!
To get jealous over bread...
(Laughing)
That's why I thought, "What a weird proverb."
Send him to Hollywood, really.
(Hobbit might be banished to Hollywood.)
- I mean... - Why would your stomach hurt...
- when the cousin buys bread? - I rushed. There's a four, though.
- There's a four. - I was wondering what that was.
(My goodness)
Take off your sunglasses.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
- We'll remove your favorite, - I won't do it from now on.
(Steak with herbs will be taken out as they failed the mission.)
herb steak.
No.
(An evenly cooked medium-rare steak)
Take the salad.
You're taking the herb steak?
- Why are you taking that? - Come on!
(The steak with herbs is out.)
Why did you have to draw the bread?
(The only high-protein dish is gone.)
There's no protein left.
Take the salad.
(Bread Man Haha ruined the 7-dish meal.)
Seriously.
Who'll do it this time?
- Let's have the best members. - I think Jong Kook...
- Yes. Go with the best members. - and I draw well.
- Let's go with the best members. - Yes, the best members.
(With their drawing skills proven, Ye Eun and Jong Kook step up.)
- Go with the best members. - Ye Eun and Jong Kook...
- I'll be the 2nd runner. - You'll be the 2nd runner.
- But Ye Eun... - Then you draw.
(Order for Round 5: Jong Kook, Ye Eun, Se Chan, Jae Seok)
- Se Chan should run last. - I'll run.
- Then you can guess it. - I'll guess it.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Jong Kook, the 1st runner checks the question.)
That's like someone who lived abroad for more than 20 years.
(Sighing)
I know this one.
(This question already has him sighing.)
(Everyone checked the question.)
They told me not to draw anything.
- This is a proverb I know. - All right.
- Ready... - Hold on. Wait!
There's no protein.
(Losing the high-protein dish puts them on edge.)
(If they get it wrong this time, even the seaweed soup will be gone.)
We should at least secure the seaweed soup.
- Wait a bit! - Split it into left and right.
Go.
Ready...
(Start)
- Go, run! - Run!
- Run! - Go!
(Moving slowly)
- Run! - Go! Run!
- Run, there's no time! - Go!
- Run! - You used five seconds.
(He used 5 seconds to draw something.)
He used ten seconds...
(He finally runs after finishing the sketch!)
Jong Kook!
You have to run!
Run!
Here.
(He divides the paper in half and hands it to Ye Eun.)
(Ace Ye Eun also adds something on each side.)
You have to run!
Run!
(Handing it over to the last player)
We were supposed to have the best members play.
(A sudden question)
Why are those two there?
Run!
(Grinning)
Five, four, three...
You have to draw something. Two, one.
(He adds a dot at the end.)
(He made it within the 30-second time limit.)
- I'm done. - What is this now?
- What is this? - It's not hard.
(Looking intently)
You can't talk to him.
It's split into left and right.
(The drawing is split into two parts.)
- They're split. - What is this?
They split it into left and right.
What is this?
You drew it like this?
I think it's a correct expression. She drew it well.
(Nervous)
- Goodness. - I added something for clarity.
What is this? Jong Kook drew this.
(Will he be able to guess it correctly despite the scribbles?)
Jong Kook took his time to draw the left side.
This is harder to decipher than ancient hieroglyphics.
- This is a proverb. - Chan Hee...
(Which proverb is this drawing about?)
We use it all the time.
- That's... - So this...
This looks like the sky.
Hold on.
(Is it related to the sky?)
Goodness.
- Okay. - Yes. What's the answer?
- I got it. - Let's go!
- I got it. - You got it.
- Even when the sky falls... - Yes.
- Even when the sky falls, - Yes.
there's always a way out.
Yes!
(Jae Seok gets 3 correct in a row.)
We did it!
- We did it! - Well done.
Well done!
(Hole, sky)
- The sky fell! - Well done.
Good job!
The sky fell!
(He put his brainpower to work and got them all right!)
Okay!
- Good job. - Even when the sky falls...
- Even when the sky falls... - We succeeded.
(The drawing is actually quite straightforward.)
- There's a hole. - That's right!
- There's always a way out. - It's a hole.
- You tried to draw a circle. - Yes. A hole.
(The Golden Hand Duo did a great job again!)
I tried to draw a circle, but my hand shook.
(They kept 5 side dishes and earned 3 darts so far!)
Who'll guess the answer this time?
Maybe Seok Jin?
We have to secure the seaweed soup and japchae.
Get set.
(Round 6 begins with the remaining 5 dishes at stake.)
Five!
(They started sprinting with 5 seconds left.)
Four, three, two, one.
(They failed due to the time limit.)
- You failed the mission. - But...
(Laughing)
It's all over your face.
- The ink? - Yes.
- Why? - You...
(He gave it his all, getting ink all over his face.)
- How did the ink get on my face? - What is it?
(And finally, Round 7!)
Okay!
(A mudskipper jumps because a gray mullet jumps.)
Just draw one mudskipper.
- A mudskipper jumping. - Okay.
Make a rough drawing!
(The keyword is quite easy. They just have to draw a mudskipper!)
Make sure it's jumping!
- Make sure it's jumping! - Okay!
(A mudskipper jumps because a gray mullet jumps.)
- I don't know what this is. - You...
You don't know what a mudskipper is, do you?
I don't.
A baby octopus jumps because a mudskipper jumps.
(They fail 2 times in a row because of the missing mudskipper.)
- No. - The mudskipper...
(Pork cutlet, French fries, and seaweed soup are gone.)
- We're only left with the salad. - No!
We're doomed.
All the main dishes are out.
(Empty)
There's no protein left.
There's no protein. This side...
There's no protein.
(It's a vegetarian meal.)
All the main dishes are here.
We lost the spicy stir-fried pork.
(Sad)
The young radish mulkimchi...
It's meaningless. Just take it out.
After seeing that we had spicy stir-fried pork...
We can just have japchae with kimchi.
(The noodle lover)
As a result,
- you got three questions right. - Three darts.
You earned three darts,
- We did well. - so you have nine darts in total.
- Nine darts? - Three isn't bad.
As a bonus...
As a bonus round...
Why don't we have the spicy stir-fried pork as the prize?
If we get it right, give us back the spicy stir-fried pork,
(They're negotiating to get spicy stir-fried pork.)
and if we get it wrong, we'll give you two dishes.
Spicy stir-fried pork!
(Food Fighter is excited.)
- Then, the bonus round will be... - Yes.
- a spicy stir-fried pork round. - Okay!
We'll remove two darts...
- if you get it wrong. - Okay.
- Nice. - But with your worst drawers.
Okay. That's fine. We can do it.
(A deal is finally struck for the bonus game.)
- It's okay. - Se Chan, Jae Seok...
(The 3 terrible artists are stepping up.)
- And me. The 3 of us. - Those 3.
- We're bad at drawing. - I'll be the one to guess.
(The one who is obsessed with spicy stir-fried pork will guess.)
- Okay. - I'll try.
- Do you want to guess, Haha? - Haha...
- Haha... - Let the Bread stay out of it.
Mr. Bread should stay out of it.
Why would the cousin buy bread?
(Drawing bread completely destroyed their trust in him.)
(Crying)
Mr. Bread should stay out of it.
(Embarrassed)
I'm sorry, Dream.
He's saying, "I'm sorry, Dream."
If we get the spicy stir-fried pork,
- it'd be like we have everything! - Okay.
- If we get spicy stir-fried pork. - Spicy stir-fried pork.
- It's the spicy stir-fried pork! - If we get spicy stir-fried pork,
- We don't need anything else. - we'd...
Real men love spicy stir-fried pork!
A man.
We can do this.
A pork.
I'll draw half of it, Jae Seok.
A trick.
Okay.
I just need to draw a tiger.
Right.
(A brilliant strategy that would make even Athena cry)
I'll draw the tiger like this...
- Let's do this. - Like this.
A team.
We just need the spicy stir-fried pork! Real men go for that!
(Their final journey to win back the spicy stir-fried pork)
We just need spicy pork!
- Let's have the spicy pork! - I want to have spicy pork!
(What they want most is what they've already lost once.)
- Please! - Please!
(The Spicy Stir-fried Pork Odyssey)
I really want to get this one right. The spicy stir-fried pork.
- What is the question? - Please.
(Jae Seok, the 1st player, checks the question.)
- Let's get it right. - Please!
You gave us an easy one.
You know...
(He gains confidence after seeing the keyword.)
They gave us an easy one.
(Will they have a happy ending?)
- Really? - Yes.
- Ready... - Is it an easy one?
- Let's do this. - Please. Spicy stir-fried pork.
Get set.
(Start)
You've got this!
I want stir-fried pork.
(Poor Artist Yu draws quickly.)
All right!
(He runs at full speed after drawing a blob with ears.)
Let's do this.
I have a feeling we'll get this one.
(I have a good feeling.)
- Please... - Let's do this.
(Serious)
Okay. Seok Jin, I think we're good.
(He hands it to Ssaebssaeb, the 2nd player.)
Here you go.
(Highly focused)
Let's get the stir-fried pork!
I believe in you guys.
(Drawing without hesitation, just as he said.)
- You have ten seconds left. - Ten seconds!
(10 seconds are left.)
- Hurry. - Run!
- Are you done? - It's complete.
(Growling!)
This is more than enough.
- He seems confident. - What?
(Excited)
- This is more than enough. - Five, four,
(Carrying the Poor Drawer Duo's drawing,)
- three, two, one. - Gosh, you're fast.
- He's fast. - One.
(he arrives with the wind at his back.)
He's the fastest man in his 60s.
You get it, right?
(Lighting up)
This is an easy one.
- The drawings are good. - A rabbit and a tiger.
(Laughing awkwardly)
Jong Kook, wait. Take your time.
- Take your time. - The drawings are solid.
(This is definitely a tiger.)
A rabbit and a tiger.
But this is a tiger.
(An unidentifiable blob)
A sheep and a tiger?
Isn't this a rabbit and a tiger? Is this a rat?
(What is this mysterious creature made by Poor Drawer Yu?)
A sheep and a tiger?
But this is a tiger.
Form a proverb with them.
A dog. Oh, right.
- All right. - Yes!
It's a dog.
(Is the blob a dog?)
- How is this a dog? - Come on.
- Form a proverb with them. - Sure.
(Will Jong Kook be able to guess it correctly...)
- What's the answer? - Let's eat some stir-fried pork.
- Let's get the stir-fried pork. - Stir-fried pork!
(and get the spicy stir-fried pork back?)
- As long as we have that... - Stir-fried pork!
- Stir-fried pork. - Am I on the right path?
- I have a feeling we'll get to eat. - Stir-fried pork.
(The fate of the spicy stir-fried pork rests in his hands!)
- Stir-fried pork, right? - Yes.
- All right! - Stir-fried pork.
What's the answer?
A newborn puppy fears no tiger.
- Yes! - That is correct.
- Yes! - Yes!
(They win back the stir-fried pork.)
- Okay! - Nice.
(The spicy stir-fried pork is back thanks to the poor drawers.)
- Good job. - Yes!
Okay!
(The stir-fried pork maniac loves it most.)
Okay.
For that correct answer, you get the stir-fried pork.
(They almost had a vegetarian meal,)
Okay!
(but a precious protein-packed dish is back.)
Stir-fried pork is all we need.
By the way, this wasn't easy at all.
- Nice. - If it wasn't for the tiger...
(That was close.)
I wouldn't have guessed if it weren't for the tiger.
I drew the tiger, and all I could think of was that.
(The tiger drawing helped him figure out the answer.)
- You did a great job. - That's solid, Se Chan.
- That's a decent drawing. - But...
You call that...
- a newborn puppy? - How else could I have drawn it?
- It's hard to guess. - Just draw a puppy.
(Seal, horse, dog)
It almost turned out to be Pikachu.
- That's a great tiger. - Pikachu, right?
(Painter Yu's animal collection is complete.)
- Pikachu. - It looks like a rabbit.
(The stir-fried pork squad heads over for lunch.)
It wasn't an easy game.
I'm starving.
You'll eat lunch with the side dishes you earned.
(They'll eat lunch with the side dishes they earned.)
- All right. - Thank you.
- It's a buffet. - Then why don't I...
- I see. - It's a buffet.
This is unbelievable.
(The side dishes they worked hard to keep)
This is great.
- I couldn't be happier. - This is amazing.
We have perilla leaves. That looks great.
(Cheering)
- Bring on the japchae. - Lettuce wraps.
(The noodle lover is excited about japchae.)
- Seok Jin. - You only get to eat this...
- at feasts. - Stay away from the japchae.
- Why? - I'll ruin your mood shortly.
I should've set him straight early on.
- Seok Jin... - You know what?
(Advice)
- can't breathe. - If a younger person gets cheeky,
set them straight on the spot. Got it?
- Breathe, Seok Jin. - It's way too late now.
(Teasing)
- You'll be annoyed forever. - Now...
All done. I can always come back for more later.
(Seok Sam got a lot of food.)
- Of course. - Absolutely.
No way.
(A bunch of leafy greens)
Is it okay to eat without washing my hands?
- Of course not. - I just washed...
- my hands. - Me too.
- That's so dirty. - What?
(Jee-rasoni is fighting multiple opponents at once as always.)
Do you need some wet wipes?
- No, I'm fine. - Dirty Seok Jin.
I'm good. Forget the wet wipes.
- I washed my hands. - I need some anyway.
(He refuses wet wipes.)
- Sure, go ahead. - Don't you need some?
- I could use some. - There's another way.
Take the lettuce like this. Watch.
Place the pork on it.
(Lonely Jee-rasoni makes a lettuce wrap...)
(without using his bare hands.)
You can eat it like this.
Like this.
(Struggling)
(He barely ate the wrap.)
- I'll enjoy. - I'll enjoy.
(He ends up using a wet wipe.)
(Jae Seok starts with the japchae.)
My gosh. No way.
(Who brought the heap of lettuce?)
(The stir-fried pork maniac)
No way.
The stir-fried pork is to die for.
- It's so good. - It's really good.
Lettuce wraps are good for your health.
(A lettuce and perilla leaf stacked together)
(All in one bite)
The stir-fried pork is amazing.
(Savoring)
It's so good.
A meal without stir-fried pork?
(Mr. Stir-fried Pork finally has his smile back.)
My gosh.
The cooks know what they're doing.
It's really good. Even the japchae is good.
The stir-fried pork is the best.
(They're all digging the lettuce wraps.)
- A piece of pork and... - The stir-fried pork is amazing.
(A now peaceful Mr. Stir-fried Pork enjoys another lettuce wrap.)
Nothing beats stir-fried pork.
Look how stir-fried pork made everyone go quiet.
(Eating)
Jong Kook's been acting cuter ever since he got married.
I can only imagine what he's like at home.
Folding it once and twice.
(Eating)
(Smirking)
When I used to be like that,
- he gave me an earful. - As for me...
He told me not to be so annoying.
Imagine if we didn't have the stir-fried pork.
(Savoring)
The meal wouldn't have been complete without it.
(My gosh)
Right?
Has he always been this silly?
He used to hate it when I acted like that.
Had he done that back on "X-Man,"
the show would've gone on for five more years.
(Chuckling)
(Kook Jong back in the day needed stir-fried pork.)
(Laughing)
In some ways,
he's the easiest person to manage.
Just give him lettuce and stir-fried pork.
Then, make sure he knows you're on the same team.
(The muscular cat is easy to handle.)
My wife has a strong memory of Chan Hee.
She was on "Let's Go! Dream Team..."
(23 years ago, Byul appeared on "Let's Go! Dream Team.")
with Lee Seoung Yeon.
- The crew was shooting... - The actress?
a jet ski jumping in the air,
and Chan Hee was behind the camera.
Something went wrong, and the jet ski came at him.
(The jet ski came at Chan Hee who was filming it.)
He jumped into the water...
because it would've hit him otherwise,
but the camera...
(A camera like this)
That big one?
He held it above water, just like in "Terminator."
(Peeking out)
- To film it? - Yes, to keep filming.
To keep the footage.
(He didn't let go of the camera to capture the scene until the end.)
My wife remembers that.
Do you remember that too?
I do.
How much was that ENG camera back then?
Back then...
The entire set cost about 100,000 dollars.
- Exactly. - He risked his own life...
- to film it. - The ENG camera?
I'm just saying he's the best.
You need that kind of mindset.
- People these days... - Even 50,000 dollars...
(Jong Kook is grabbing more leafy greens.)
was a lot of money back then.
They all want it easy these days.
Right? Who agrees?
(A heap)
- I need more pork. - Can you get me more lettuce?
- Sure. Have some of mine. - That's the last of it.
(He's feeling generous after eating all that pork.)
You know...
(Taking everything down to the last piece)
- It's so good. - He's cleaning the bowl.
Serve up stir-fried pork, and nobody complains.
(Satisfied after a simple meal of stir-fried pork)
- I'm so full. - I ate so much.
What a meal.
The last game...
(The final mission to earn darts)
is Empty Heads Pay the Price.
- Okay! - You will answer quizzes...
while jumping rope.
- What? - Oh, no.
- This sounds impossible. - You'll go in one at a time,
- This. - but only after...
successfully answering a question.
(What's the birthday song Jae Seok made for Seok Jin's 60th birthday?)
("Happy Birthday, Jee Seok Jin")
After giving the correct answer?
Yes. Once all players get in and start jumping rope,
you must complete three jumps...
- to win. - Three jumps.
So it's like this.
We have to answer correctly to start jumping rope.
(A test of both smarts and stamina)
If you fail, we'll cut back on your darts and lower...
the required number of players.
- So it's like this. - Hold on.
Those with high stamina should go first.
Jae Seok, no.
(Stern)
Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and I will try to get it started.
(Pointing out)
- If it's something we can answer. - But...
- What we can answer... - But can we keep going?
- You won't have the stamina. - We need to answer correctly first.
- It's sad to hear you say that. - So...
(A brutally honest self-assessment)
Answer it if it's something...
- you know. - He thinks we should buy bread...
- if our cousin buys land. - Why buy bread?
Tell me about it.
- How stupid am I? - Mr. Bread.
I'm asking out of pure curiosity.
Has Dream ever mentioned it?
- All the time. - I see.
What does he say?
Whenever I'm teaching So Wool math,
(So Wool, Haha's second son)
he laughs from right behind me.
(Laughing)
That'd be fun to watch.
- It's funny. - He thinks it's hilarious.
He knew about my English when he was four.
He realized it was off.
When he was four?
(Dream realized it too soon.)
You shouldn't speak English in front of kids.
Exactly. You'll get burned.
- But since this is... - How hard is the quiz?
a team jump rope challenge,
- Ji Hyo and Ye Eun should go last. - Yes, last.
(In a group jump-rope challenge, stamina is key.)
- That's right. - They can't go first.
Jae Seok has the stamina, so...
- I'll go first. - Yes, you go first.
I'll go first.
(Jae Seok, who has great stamina, goes first.)
Jong Kook, why don't you go second?
- I'll go first. - Sure thing.
(Jong Kook goes 2nd despite his bad ankle.)
- Got it. Okay. - Number two and...
The rope is heavy-duty.
- That's going to hurt. - Look at them.
(The strong guys step in to turn the rope.)
I'm sure they'll do a good job.
- They're in great shape. - They look like they have stamina.
- Jae Seok, Jong Kook, - Let's do this!
(Order for Round 1)
Seok Jin,
Haha, me, Ji Hyo, and Ye Eun. In that order.
Going last puts the pressure on.
That's the order of our intelligence.
- Okay, here we go. - Jae Seok, I'm scared.
(Everyone will give it a try in Round 1.)
(If they succeed, they'll earn 7 darts.)
Let's bring it in, guys.
- Go, team. - Let's go.
- Over here. One, two, three, go! - One, two, three, go!
(Sighing)
- All right. - Get ready.
(Round 1 starts.)
- And... - Jae Seok goes first.
What's the question?
(Name 3 Joseon kings.)
What is it?
Great King Sejong, King Jeongjo, King Yeongjo.
(Correct)
- That's it. - Go.
(Jae Seok, the first player, is in.)
- Okay. - It's fine so far.
(What is Korea's 1st national treasure?)
Our first national treasure? It's... It's Sungnyemun!
Okay. He's right, yes?
(Sungnyemun is correct.)
Why is everyone so smart?
Here goes.
(What is Jae Seok's date of birth?)
- Jae Seok's... - Seventy...
August 14, 1972?
Okay.
(Correct)
(Seok Jin got in safely.)
(The smarter members have all played.)
This is insane.
(What was the world's first woodblock print?)
(This question is...)
- You know this. - Me!
Of the existing xylographs, what is the oldest in the world?
(It came up many times on Running Man.)
The Jikji.
(He got it wrong last time.)
(What about this time?)
Me!
The Great Dharani Sutra!
(Answer: The Great Dharani Sutra)
- Okay. Get in here. - Why are you all so good?
(Correct)
Okay.
(Jong Kook's slowly losing form.)
Why are you all so good?
(Which day has the longest night of the year?)
The longest night? Dongji!
(Correct)
- You're so good. - Let's go!
(Even Se Chan got in.)
- Let's go! - Looking good.
(Will they succeed on the first try?)
Why are you all so good? This is crazy.
(Who's the scholar who wrote...)
Scholar who wrote...
("Sounds of the Language" and "Grammar of the National Language?")
"Sounds of the Language," "Grammar of the National Language"
- It's... What's his name? - Who is it?
(She doesn't know the answer?)
What's his name?
(They're on the verge of success!)
What's going on?
- Ju Si Gyung! - Correct.
(Ju Si Gyung is the correct answer.)
(She just has to jump in!)
Get in here!
(The others are getting tired.)
Hurry up!
- Get in here! - Ji Hyo!
(Flinching)
(Ji Hyo jumps in.)
(What will happen?)
Hurry up!
- Who was it? - I couldn't join in.
(Her foot got caught.)
Hurry up!
- Who was it? - Who was it?
- Who was it? - I couldn't join in.
(Sorry)
- Oh, dear. - Ji Hyo!
Come on.
- Ji Hyo! - How could you fail that?
(They failed in Round 1.)
Hey, Ji Hyo.
(My gosh)
(Smirking)
- Ji Hyo... - All that jumping...
I'm too scared to jump in.
(Intimidated)
- You should've practiced, then! - Practice!
- Practice. - You should practice.
- This is no joke. - Jump in on the snap.
(Jae Seok started off, so he's exhausted now.)
Ji Hyo. Jump in when you hear the snap.
Did I give the correct answer?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Why can't you jump in? - Dongji...
(It seems Se Chan made a wild guess.)
I got Dongji right.
(Proud)
(Yang Empty Head is proud of himself.)
- What? - Dongji.
- Dongji? - I don't remember the question.
We should...
- The Great Dharani Sutra. - The longest...
(I'm proud of myself too.)
My throat hurts.
(While they're celebrating together,)
I got Dongji right.
I want to practice too!
- Practice. - Go ahead.
(the Empty Head Sisters practice jumping rope.)
- You should practice. - I want to practice.
Go on.
(Surprised)
Go in now.
- Snap and go. - Snap and go. That's it.
- Yes! - Go a bit forward!
- Move forward. - Snap and go.
- Go! Go now! - Why won't you jump in?
- Jump in on the snap. - Snap and go!
(Trainer Kook is toughening her up.)
- Try again. - Hey!
- Practice. Go on. - Try again.
- It's been 16 years. - Go!
- Cue. - Go!
- Go! Good. - Go!
- What... - On the snap.
Jump in as soon as you hear the smack. Ji Hyo.
Did you forget what to do?
- Do you feel unwell? - You did this for 16 years.
- Come in. - Go!
Go!
(They've been jumping rope together for 16 years.)
- For 16 years... - Listen.
(Ji Hyo is also frustrated that her body isn't cooperating.)
- I failed to jump in for 16 years. - Wait.
Jump in on cue of the snap.
- That's best. - I get the theory, but I can't.
- Try again. - Jump in on cue.
(She gives it another shot, trusting her muscle memory.)
We'll count you in.
Let's do this. Do you guys mind?
- Let's go. - It doesn't hurt anyway.
- It's not that. - Don't be afraid.
- Two, three, and go. - Go now!
- That's it. - That's it.
(She finally jumped in.)
- That's it. - She did it.
(There's hope!)
- Stop now. - She did it.
- But... - That's what you do.
You can jump in a bit slower.
(After failing Round 1, there are fewer challengers and darts left.)
You failed to get 7 in a row, so now it's down to 6.
(If 6 of them make it, they'll receive 6 darts.)
- You're down one. - Six people.
- Hey. - Let's do a group cheer.
- Let's do this. - Chan Hee, Kang Chan Hee.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
Who wants to drop out?
Ji Hyo or me, one or the other.
Answer a question and jump in.
The questions are pretty tough.
I'll go first if it's something I know.
- Yes. Do that. - Good idea.
(Empty Heads will jump in first if they know the answer.)
Go for it if you know it.
- Answer and jump in. - For me...
- I'm scared I'll get it wrong. - Me too.
- Stamina... - Go if you know the answer.
(Will their strategy of going first pay off?)
- Guess and go. - I have the energy.
- Yes. - Sure.
(Round 2 starts.)
- Ready? - Guess and go.
- Get set. - I might get it wrong.
I might too.
(Which American physicist is known...)
- The atom bomb... - The atom bomb...
(as the "father of the atomic bomb?")
- Me! - Oppenheimer.
- Jae Seok, I was... - Jump in.
(Correct)
It was... I was going to answer that.
- Me! - Oppenheimer.
(Haha was going to go first if he knew the answer.)
- Jae Seok, I was... - Jump in.
It was... I was going to answer that.
(He lost his chance.)
- Go for the next one. - Oppenheimer...
(I knew the answer.)
(Whose birthday did the government announce as Teachers' Day?)
- Go for the next one. - Oppenheimer...
Whose birthday did the government announce as Teachers' Day?
- Great King Sejong. - Jump in.
(Answer: Great King Sejong)
I don't know that. How did he know that?
(He missed the answer again.)
How do you know that?
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook go first, ignoring strategy and planning.)
(Who wrote the world -famous classic "The Little Prince?")
- Alright. - How do they know that?
"The Little Prince"...
- Me! - Go for it.
- Saint-Exupéry. - That's it.
(Correct!)
- Saint-Exupéry. - Go.
Good. Hurry up!
(Haha manages to join in.)
(Name the person who founded Children's Day,)
Childrens' Day. What's the answer?
(including his pen name and real name.)
- What is it? - Sopa Bang Jeong Hwan.
- How do you know that? - I had no idea.
(Correct)
(All three of them were clueless.)
- How do you know that? - I had no idea.
Seok Jin, move forward.
(What's the southernmost island of Korea?)
It's fine. What are these questions?
The southernmost island...
- Jeju Island? - Incorrect.
Ulleung Island?
- Ulleung Island! - Incorrect!
- Dokdo? - Dokdo?
(The others are suffering.)
What's wrong?
- What's wrong? - Jump in.
Incorrect.
(What's the southernmost island of Korea?)
Ulleung Island?
- Ulleung Island! - Incorrect!
- Dokdo? - Dokdo?
- Incorrect. - Come on!
(The Empty Head Siblings are just wasting time.)
Se Chan!
- Seriously. - Incorrect.
- The southernmost island? - Se Chan!
- Geoje Island! - Incorrect!
- Ulleung Island? - Ulleung Island?
Gageo Island!
(In the end, the rope caught their feet.)
Darn it! What's the question?
- What is it? - What's the southernmost island?
(What's the southernmost island of Korea?)
It's Marado!
(Answer: Mara Island)
- Isn't it Marado? - Marado!
- It's Marado. - Marado...
(They fail in Round 2.)
- Marado... - You don't know Marado?
- It wasn't that hard. - I named all the islands I knew.
(Sighing)
- My gosh... - What?
Isn't it Marado?
(Jae Seok's worn out.)
- Marado... - You don't know Marado?
Oppenheimer.
(After answering the first question)
- Jae Seok, I was... - Jump in.
It was... I was going to answer that.
(Jae Seok's jump-rope count: 2)
(Jae Seok was the 1st to start jumping.)
(Jae Seok's jump-rope count: 23)
(Sped up 4 times)
(Jae Seok's jump-rope count: 41)
- Hey! - Ulleung Island?
- Gageo Island. - Incorrect.
(He jumped 41 times without stopping!)
Seriously.
How many times did I...
(He jumped nearly 100 times in total, including Round 1.)
I think I jumped 100 times.
Me too.
Seok Jin. We're clueless, and we need someone to stay back.
Then this time, you guys go first.
- Yes, go first. - Yes.
How many people are there this time?
(There will be 5 challengers this time.)
- Let's take a break. - Five.
(If they make it, they'll earn 5 darts.)
Then us two will back out.
(Excluding Ye Eun and Ji Hyo)
- Why... You go first. - I'll go in first.
(Se Chan, who isn't worn out yet, goes first.)
- We have to... - I'm breaking a sweat.
Your shoulders might hurt. I have to get it right.
Give me lots of time.
(How many attempts will it take him to jump in?)
I'm so glad we had lunch.
- Yes. - We'd have failed otherwise.
(Round 3 starts.)
You're down to five. Ready?
(What's the battle Admiral Yi Sun Sin won with 12 boats?)
The battle Admiral Yi Sun Sin won with 12 boats...
- Go! - Battle of Hansan Island?
(Answer: Battle of Myeongnyang)
Battle of Hanbando.
- What? - Incorrect.
(Laughing incredulously)
- Noryang. - Noryangjin.
(Having no expectations)
Try something else.
- Hansan. Hanban. - It's a movie title.
- Myeongnyang! - Correct!
(He barely got it right.)
My gosh. This is hilarious.
(Who established the Mongolian Empire?)
- What? - This one...
Me! Genghis Khan!
Yes, that's it. Go.
(Correct)
Go a bit forward.
(Haha and Se Chan jumped in first this time.)
I want to poop. I'm done for.
(What does the Korean word "golchi" mean?)
- "Golchi?" - The Korean word "golchi"...
- Head and teeth. - Head and teeth?
(Incorrect)
- Teeth. - This part.
What's this called?
(Seok Jin doesn't seem to know either!)
- What's this? - Teeth?
(The first two are tired already.)
- Hurry up! - What's this?
- Teeth! - Teeth?
(Trying not to poop)
This. What's this called?
- The temples! - The temples.
It's not that? Your whole face.
- Incorrect. - Your head!
- That's right. - Okay.
("Head" is correct.)
(What is the most widely grown grain in the world?)
- Corn. - Correct.
(Got it in one go!)
(They need just one more person.)
That's it!
(They succeed if Jong Kook can join in.)
(His pants are slipping down!)
What's happening?
(What is the native Korean word for a female pheasant?)
- What? - "Kkaturi!"
("Kkaturi" is correct!)
- Correct! - What?
- "Kkaturi!" - Correct!
- Go! - Okay!
- One, two! - One, two!
(Everyone including Jong Kook is in.)
(If they jump 3 times from now on, they'll succeed!)
- Two, three! - Two, three!
(Will they succeed this time?)
- One, two, three! - One, two, three!
- We did it! - That's it!
(The mission is complete!)
- Did we do it? - Okay!
- Okay. - Well done.
(They made it on their 3rd attempt.)
- We did it. - What a relief.
- Good job. - We did it.
(Applause)
- We did it. - It was close toward the end.
(They got 5 more darts.)
Well done.
- That was close. - "Golchi" was a tough one.
- I can't do it anymore. - Fortunately,
I got something I knew.
- What was it? - Kkaturi.
(These two are too ashamed to face Chan Hee.)
Ji Hyo and Ye Eun. Are you not participating?
(They feel sorry for no reason.)
- What about them? - How about a round just for them?
- For two darts. - Give them a chance.
(They want to give the Empty Head Sisters a chance to contribute.)
- For two darts. - For just two.
(They'll put 2 darts on the line and try again.)
- Sounds good. - Okay.
- Sounds good. - For two darts?
Are you ready?
(The bonus round starts.)
Whoever gets it right goes first.
Get set.
(Who wrote "Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind,")
(a book about the history of humankind?)
"Sapiens?"
You know this.
- I know the answer! - Hey.
(It's on the tip of her tongue.)
I know...
- It came up recently. - Homo? Homo Sapiens.
Incorrect.
It was on a recent episode.
(This question was even asked recently!)
One or the other.
"Yu?"
(Answer: Yuval Harari)
One or the other. Get it right.
(The Empty Head Sisters aren't even trying.)
"Yu?"
(They keep spinning the rope.)
Why can't anyone jump in?
Their arms are hurting.
(Almost reaching their limits)
- "Yu?" - Yu-something.
His arm is aching.
- Yu... Yuval Harari. - His poor arms.
(Answer: Yuval Harari)
- What? - Yuval Harari?
- Correct. - What do I do now?
(Ji Hyo remembered!)
- Yuval Harari? - Correct.
What do I do now?
- What now? - She's in.
(She jumped in at once.)
The next question.
What? Seoul, Busan...
(Name all six metropolitan cities in South Korea.)
(Answer: Busan, Daegu, Incheon, Daejeon, Ulsan)
- Seoul's a metropolitan city. - Incorrect.
- Busan. - What?
- Ji Hyo... - Give up.
(Their challenge ended in failure.)
You failed.
It's way too difficult!
- Incheon. - Give them another chance...
- Busan, Daegu. - for them.
Give them one more chance.
- It's fun. - Let us try again.
- Give Ye Eun another chance. - Please give us one more chance.
- Let Ye Eun try it once. - One more chance.
(With the goal of giving the gift to Director Kang,)
- Let her try it once. - You can do it for one dart.
(they put 1 dark on the line and try again.)
- Okay. - We'll turn the rope.
- It's too exhausting. - Give it to me.
- Get ready. - The one who answers first...
(The Empty Head Sisters' 2nd attempt)
- will enter first. - Set.
This is better, right?
(What's the capital of Argentina? Answer: Buenos Aires)
The capital of Argentina?
Madrina?
- Incorrect. - For goodness' sake.
What even is Madrina? You didn't even say Madrid.
- Argentina? - It's so funny.
The capital of Argentina.
- Madrid? - It's hard for her.
- Luxembourg? - Incorrect.
- Is it long? - Hey, let's just...
give up.
- Pass. Give us another question. - Another question.
- Give us one more question. - One more question.
(The Hopeless Sisters want to prove themselves at least once.)
- One more question. - This one is extremely easy.
(Writer: "This one is extremely easy.")
- Okay. - It's very easy.
(They give them one las chance for Director Kang.)
They're out of questions. This is your last chance.
Madrina.
(Empty Head Sisters' last attempt)
- All right. - The dancing
- Little Madrina - Here it comes. Get ready.
(Who is the father of mathematics? Answer: Pythagoras)
- Handel. - Incorrect.
(What?)
Hey, he is a musician.
(She named someone from a completely different field.)
- Please. - He is a musician.
- The father of mathematics? - The father of mathematics.
Who is the father of mathematics?
- "The Art of Mathematics." - Incorrect.
(Confident)
- "The Art of Mathematics." - Mathematics.
Mathematics. Is he a foreigner?
- Of course. - It's...
Py... Pythagoras.
Correct.
(She finally gets a correct answer!)
- Pythagoras. - Correct.
- Okay. - Come on in.
- That's it. - Come on in.
(Ddochi is finally jumping rope for the first time.)
- One. - Ye Eun, go forward.
(Next is Ji Hyo.)
- The next question. - The next question.
- Give her the next question. - You punk!
- You need to answer a question! - For goodness' sake.
(She didn't see the question.)
You need to answer a question!
(Empty Head Chicken)
Let's just stop.
- Quit it. - Let's just stop.
(She was so fired up that she jumped in without seeing the question.)
- Let's stop. - You failed the mission.
(They failed the bonus mission.)
- Quit it. - Seriously.
- No, let's stop. - You failed.
- Let's stop. That's enough. - Seriously.
- She jumped in like a tiger moth. - Let's stop.
(All that jumping and rope-spinning wore him out.)
I mean...
Hey, Madrina.
"The Art of Mathematics."
(Madrina Ji is her new English name.)
Your English name is Madrina from now on.
With the results of your last mission,
(Adding 5 darts they earned through mission)
the total number of darts you have is 14.
- Fourteen? - Yes.
Using 14 darts,
(Number of darts: 14)
- you'll have the last darts match. - Where will it take place?
- We should've gotten two more. - That would've been nice.
(The climax of the day)
- This is... - This place is...
(A dart showdown...)
- You know... - It'll be hard.
(for Chan Hee's gift)
One hundred points.
- Times three. - It isn't the dartboard I know.
(Serious)
Chan Hee, I'll throw them well.
- I'll do my best. - Good luck.
How will we beat a professional?
(A custom-made dartboard)
No, I'm sure the professional hasn't done this.
- I'm sure this is new for him. - The height is different.
(Chan Hee's warriors are feeling confident.)
We really should give...
- some presents to Chan Hee. - That's right.
(The dart rules are revealed.)
The final darts match...
- for Chan Hee's presents... - Okay.
consists of three rounds.
Every time you win a round, you can take...
- the associated present. - Okay.
The present for Round One is a joint supplement.
The present for Round Two is Onnuri gift certificates.
The present for Round Three is wild ginseng.
Okay.
The professional darts player will throw three darts per round.
- Three darts per round? - Yes.
You'll have 14 darts you've collected...
and one bonus dart from us.
- In total, you'll have 15 darts. - Thank you.
Use them as you want...
(The one with the higher score wins in each round.)
to get a higher score and win the round.
If you feel like...
- you won't win this round, - Shall we give up?
you can give up on the present and focus on the next round.
We divide up 15 darts for 3 rounds, right?
- That's right. - Okay.
If we mess up from the start, we should give up on that round.
- It'll be better to give up. - Good.
If you lose all three rounds,
Chan Hee will only get the chair, the most basic present.
(Only the basic item, a chair, will be gifted.)
- So please do your best. - No, we got this. Don't worry.
Let's distract our competitor by chatting next to him.
(We can ask him to have a drink with us sometime.)
We can ask him to have a drink with us sometime. Don't worry.
- Now, - Okay.
(Today's opponent makes his entrance.)
I'll introduce the player for the darts match.
Please come on in.
Sir, please come on in.
Gosh, it has been a while.
(They've never met.)
Sir.
(A professional dart player walks in.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Please come this way.
- Son Heung Min? - Son Heung Min?
(What?)
- Son Heung Min? - He really looks like him.
- I mean... - He has the same looks.
- He really looks like him. - He really looks like Heung Min.
Hello, my name is Lee Se Hyun,
(A Korea Soft Darts Association player, Lee Se Hyun)
and I'm Korea's professional soft darts player.
(Bullseye)
He is relaxed.
One more.
If he gets good points for this...
(3 times in a row)
(The Son Heung Min lookalike who took the darts scene by storm,)
All right. It's 47.
He really looks like him.
Please do this once.
He looks like him.
(It seems he's done it many times.)
- He really looks like him. - He looks like him.
For how long have you played darts?
I've played darts for 14 years.
He has frequented darts bars since the 90s.
(He used to play darts in Apgujeong.)
- He is a professional. - When it comes to experience...
You're a senior.
- I've played darts for 25 years. - Yes.
You'll only have...
- three darts per round. - Yes.
How many points can you get with three darts?
If you put your heart into it.
- If I use this dartboard, - Three hundred points.
I'll need to get 300 points using 3 darts.
(Right here)
He can do it.
- I see. - Do you have tips?
One tip I have is...
keeping the body still...
- and using only the arm. - Only the arm.
- You only use this part. - Only the hand moves.
(Like this)
You throw with your wrist.
- What if I do this? - Getting closer to the dartboard...
won't necessarily make you better.
(They're getting some pro tips from their opponent.)
- I see. - You throw like this, right?
- That's right. - I have a question.
- Like shooting a basketball. - Should it go in a straight line...
or in a curved line?
Throwing it in a curved line will give you more advantage.
- That's right. - May we have some practice time?
(It's time to practice.)
- Sure. - Okay.
We're good at darts.
- We're good. - Let's come up with a strategy.
Se Hyun, where are you from?
- I'm from Paju. - Really?
I'm from Paju too.
(He's from Dongducheon.)
He is from Paju.
(Se Chan approaches his target.)
You're from Paju.
(Jae Seok begins to practice.)
Our strategy...
- Here. - The height is different.
(Fail)
Gosh, Jae Seok.
- We need a good strategy. - Here.
(Next is a loud middle-aged man.)
This is how you do it. Watch.
Throw it.
(He's eliminated.)
- It's hard. - Is it hard?
Throw it. Like this.
If you do this...
- Where should I look when I throw? - Which part should I hold?
When I do it,
- I look at the red ring by 20. - Right?
- That's the spot. - Yes.
Do I throw it like this?
It's better to hold this part...
for the center of gravity because the back part is light.
(The girl with the hunched back is determined to learn.)
Let me practice. Let me try it once.
All right.
(15 times 2 is 30 points!)
You did well. It's a double.
- A double. - A double.
(Next is Ji Hyo.)
- Se Hyun. - Not bad.
(Not bad)
Don't you need to practice?
(It's Se Hyun's turn.)
Can you hit 100 at once?
- One hundred? - Usually...
- Hit it three times. - Right there.
(A demonstration from the player who competes globally)
- Usually... - Hit it three times.
Right there.
- Did he do that on purpose? - He is nervous.
(1 point)
- What? Why didn't it work? - One point.
- It isn't easy. - Exactly.
(The second shot)
- It's not his usual dartboard. - Four points.
(4 points)
You're about my level.
(How about the third shot?)
Seriously.
(Fortunately, that's 100 points!)
- Of course. - He adjusted his shots.
You throw the darts from the top.
That's good.
(Another 100-point shot!)
- He zeroed in. - That's right.
- Seriously. - He did it. He zeroed in.
(Despite the distractions, he quickly found his aim.)
- He is a professional. - A professional is different.
From the top to the bottom.
(Next is a longtime darts player.)
- Darts bar. - All right.
(It's quite close to the center!)
- He got it. - Mr. Darts Bar.
Darts bar. Mr. Darts Bar.
Darts bar.
What's up with him?
(He hit the same spot again.)
- Seok Jin. - He hit the same spot.
- Frequenting darts bars helped. - You're William Tell.
- Seok Jin, you're good. - Was it okay?
(William Tell is an ancient term for a good shot.)
He is William Tell.
- Seok Jin, you're good. - Was it okay?
It'll be nice to get 100 points.
(Next up is Jae Seok.)
Aim for 100 points.
If you get 100 points, we'll begin right away.
That's good.
(100 points)
(Jae Seok also did a good job!)
- My goodness. - What? How is he so good at it?
Let's just give it a go.
- Shall we begin? - Okay.
(They've got the hang of it, so they end practice right away.)
- You're good. - Let's go.
Round One is for a joint supplement.
The yellow circle is 100 points.
The red ring is double.
The green ring is triple.
Se Hyun will go first...
- and throw three darts. - Okay.
- Let's use all of them. - In that case... Three darts.
- His score will be important. - Yes.
- Of course. - The line...
- He stepped on the line. - He stepped on the line.
- We get sensitive about this. - We're sensitive.
(The mind game begins.)
- Don't step on the line. - We're sensitive like that.
You need to say, "Here I go."
- "Here I go." - Here I go.
Okay.
- He is nervous. - We'll win.
It's more nerve-racking than a competition.
- Right. - Se Hyun.
(How will nervous Se Hyun's first shot go?)
- His form is very stable. - Once he zeroes in...
(100 points!)
He doesn't disappoint.
(100 points again!)
- What? - Will he get 300 points?
- What's the score? - So...
What's the score?
(He actually gets 300 points.)
- What's the score? - So what's the score?
(Professional: 300, Members: 0)
Se Hyun got 300 points.
(They need to get over 300 points for the joint supplement.)
- All right. - What?
- All right. - Three hundred points.
Let's do this.
- You must throw at least three. - We need to do that, right?
(They need to throw at least 3 darts in each round.)
- You should do it. - You should do it.
- Get 100 points. - We can't get over 300 points.
(Ddochi is up against...)
How will he beat him?
He is really good. He is a professional.
Hey, you're stepping on the line.
(the top score of 300 points.)
You need to go back further.
- Here I go. - Do I throw it like this?
It's better to hold this part...
(Ye Eun even got a 1-on-1 lesson.)
for the center of gravity because the back part is light.
I see. This part.
All right.
(She got 30 points during practice.)
A double.
You need to go back further.
(How many points will she get this time?)
- Here I go. - We can't beat a professional.
- Say, "Here I go." - "Here I go."
Here I go.
It's...
Madrina.
Madrina, why...
(She misses.)
Madrina, why are you so weak?
(Remaining darts: 14)
- Madrina. - What's wrong with you?
(Madrina wasted a precious shot.)
Madrina, you're too much.
You're too much, Madrina.
I'm not stepping on the line, right?
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
- Go ahead. - Twenty.
(She also did pretty well during practice.)
- Not bad. - Okay.
(Will she do well?)
- Go ahead. - Twenty.
Twenty.
(19 points!)
- Nineteen. - Let's give up on this round.
(Professional: 300, Members: 19)
Let's give up on this round.
- We need to throw three darts. - Let's give up.
(Remaining darts: 13)
- One more. - We need to throw one more.
- We need to throw one more. - We have to.
- Throw two darts. - Three.
(Jae Seok will throw a third shot.)
- We need to throw one more. - Go ahead.
Move out of the way.
I'll look at 20.
- Okay. Double. That's good. - Okay.
(17 times 2 is 34 points.)
- Not bad. - Die.
- We'll give up on Round One. - Die.
(Professional: 300, Members: 53, Remaining darts: 12)
We'll give up on Round One.
(They only throw 3 darts.)
Die.
Let's give up.
(They make a strategic choice to give up on Round 1.)
Madrina can't do it.
How will we beat him?
(Joint supplement: Fail)
- You lost the joint supplement. - Take it.
You have 12 darts left.
(Remaining darts: 12)
- I'll give him joint supplements. - Yes.
(The face of the supplement)
- Let's do well this time. - Let's do that.
(Thank you.)
(Only the Round 2 Onnuri gift certificates...)
- Onnuri gift certificates. - That's right.
(and Round 3 wild ginseng remain.)
Isn't wild ginseng better?
- Gift certificates are better. - Gift certificates are better.
Do you prefer Onnuri gift certificates...
- or wild ginseng? - Gift certificates, of course.
- How much are they worth? - Three hundred dollars.
- Onnuri gift certificates. - Really? I prefer wild ginseng.
- Wild ginseng? - Wild ginseng.
(He likes wild ginseng more than Onnuri gift certificates.)
I bet wild ginseng is more expensive.
- Okay. - Let's get the wild ginseng.
(Joint supplement: Fail)
Chan Hee, we'll throw the darts well.
- Let's check out his score. - Let's check out his score first.
(Round 2, with Onnuri gift certificates on the line, begins.)
Round Two is for Onnuri gift certificates.
Please say, "Here I go."
- Here I go. - Your form is so cool.
- He is stepping on the line. - Thank you.
(Keeping him in check again)
- He is stepping on the line. - I'm not stepping on it.
- Start chatting. - Let's have a drink sometime.
(Discreet)
(Round 2, the professional makes his 1st shot.)
So that's how you hold it.
Okay.
(4 points!)
Okay. We have a chance.
- It's our chance. - For goodness' sake.
(Darn it...)
- We have a chance. Let's win. - We're sorry.
(It's his second shot.)
- It's our chance. - We have a chance.
(Chatting loudly)
- Okay. - Okay.
- It's our chance. - We have a chance.
- It's our chance. - Hey.
(4 points again!)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Shocked)
Oh, my.
(He got 8 points after throwing 2 darts.)
Hold on a second.
- All right. Don't be nervous. - We'll win.
- We'll win. - We're sorry.
(His last shot)
Let's win.
He zeroed in.
- Let's win. Come on. - He zeroed in.
(Will he be able to overcome the noisy background?)
- My goodness. - He is incredible.
One hundred.
(His last shot is 100 points!)
- My goodness. - He is incredible.
(Professional: 108, Members)
- It's 108 points. - If it's 108 points...
(It isn't an impossible score to beat!)
Once we get 100 points...
(Remaining darts: 12)
Okay.
Then we'll have a chance.
- All right. - It's doable.
- Let's go. - Twelve darts remain.
- Yes, 12 darts remain. - We can use many darts.
- Who will go 1st? - Seok Sam, go 1st.
(Seok Sam is the first to go for the Onnuri gift certificates.)
Seok Jin, get 100 points.
I'll give it a go.
- I'll go after Seok Sam. - What's this?
- Me too. I'll throw a dart too. - I need to get 100 points.
(Pressured)
- I have a good feeling about this. - Let's see how well he does.
- From the back... - Here I go.
(The man who frequented dart bars gives it a go.)
Shoot.
Nice pinky finger position. That's a good position.
I'll have so much respect if he gets 100 points.
Shoot.
(18 points)
- You didn't say, "Here I go." - Eighteen.
(Scheming)
- You didn't say, "Here I go." - I didn't say, "Here I go."
(Joining right away)
Start over.
(They begin scheming as always.)
- If I get 100 points... - Listen.
- Don't forget to say, "Here I go." - Say it before you begin.
- Start over. - Exactly.
It can't be helped.
(Sly)
- It's okay. - It's a rule.
- Don't forget to say, "Here I go." - Say it before you begin.
- Start over. - Exactly.
(Taking back 18 points)
You need to say it.
- I'll let you off this once. - It's rude not to say it.
(Letting it slide just this once)
- Say, "Here I go." - Here I go.
- You need to say, "Here I go." - Here I go.
- Seriously. - "Here I go."
Can you put down the pinky finger? I don't think it's helping.
He wants to make a promise.
With whom?
- You know, - The afterlife.
his form is...
- His form is so cool. - He already made a promise.
(Pretending not to have heard it)
- It's a promise with the afterlife. - The afterlife.
(Attacking again)
(Exploding)
- Hey. - "I'll go by that time."
(What did you just say?)
- Just throw the dart. - Listen.
- I'm holding a dart. Be careful. - I mean...
- I mean... - The afterlife.
- A promise with the afterlife. - He already made a promise.
Se Hyun, isn't it too much?
- A promise that you'll go later. - The afterlife.
Please give them a scolding.
- Later on... - Please say, "You're mean."
A promise that you'll go later.
(Don't get me wrong.)
- "I'll go later." - That's right. "I can't go now."
(Jae Seok just wished Seok Sam's long life.)
- "Tell them that I can't go now." - "I promise to go later."
- "Tell them that I can't go now." - That's right.
(Back to the 1st dart of Round 2)
Did you say, "Here I go?"
- Here I go. - He said it earlier.
I hope he gets 100 points.
(What will he get after nullifying 18 points?)
- Gosh. - Seok Jin.
- Gosh. - Seok Jin, it was close.
(17 points)
- Seventeen. - The direction was nice.
(Professional: 108, Members: 17)
- We have a chance. - You can tell...
- that he has frequented darts bars. - Yes.
(Kook Jong goes next.)
It's different when I actually throw it.
- Like this. - Get 100, and we'll win.
Get 100, and we'll win.
(If they get 100 points now, they'll get the gift certificates.)
It's... You know,
- I shouldn't focus on it too much. - That's right.
(Muttering)
- That's right. - I'll throw it haphazardly.
As I say, "I don't care whether we win or lose..."
(Muttering)
Shoot.
(13 points)
- Gosh. - Thirteen points.
You're so bad at throwing.
For goodness' sake. Seriously.
(Professional: 108, Members: 30)
- Now... - Haha, can you do it?
- Thirty points. - You're so bad at throwing.
It's okay.
I'll just take the chair.
- We have 30 points. - We have 30 points.
(Remaining darts: 10)
It's okay.
- Will you go next? - Thirteen points.
- Here I go. - One hundred points.
Go ahead. Get 100 points, and we'll win.
Get 100 points, and we'll win.
(Haha gives it a go when they need 100 points.)
- Go ahead. You can do it. - Otherwise...
The center.
- Gosh. - Hey, it's a double.
- Let's throw one more dart. - It's a double.
- Four? - Move.
- It's 13 times 2. - Is it 13 times 2?
(Professional: 108, Members: 56)
Yes, it's 13 times 2.
(Remaining darts: 9)
- It's meaningless. - The current score is 56 points.
- We must get the gift certificates. - That's right.
- Let's throw one more dart. - Seok Jin.
We'll end up using all the darts.
Let's throw 1 more dart. Just 1 more dart.
(It's either they use more darts...)
We need to get the wild ginseng.
(or go to Round 3 after wrapping up.)
How much is the wild ginseng?
It's 500 dollars.
All right. We must get 100 points. Give it a go.
(They decide to throw just one more.)
- Get 100 points, and we'll win. - Here I go.
- Please. - I'll just...
(Se Chan will go.)
- Otherwise, - I'll just throw hard.
- get 20 times 2 or something. - Get 20.
Look over here.
- I'll throw hard. - Hit this spot for 60 points.
- That's right. - Hit this spot...
(Professional: 108, Members: 56)
for 40 points.
- Get it in that line. - That line.
(They desperately need a high score.)
- One hundred points or up there. - All right.
- Say, "Here I go." - I tend to throw them quickly.
Here I go.
- He might succeed in it. - You never know.
My goodness. Three points.
(Se Chan's 3 points)
- Three points. - One more.
(Professional: 108, Members: 59)
Let's throw one more dart.
(Remaining darts: 8)
- You throw it. - Stop.
- One more. - We need to stop.
Did he say, "Here I go?"
Let's throw one more dart.
- You throw it. - Stop.
- One more. - We need to stop.
- One more. - Let's go for the wild ginseng.
Why would you give up on the gift certificates?
We need to go for the wild ginseng.
- The wild ginseng. - Seok Jin.
Seok Jin, this is our chance.
- Let's go for the wild ginseng. - Isn't this...
- our chance? - Let's go for the wild ginseng.
- Just one more dart. - The professional might get...
- three hundred points next time. - One more.
Thanks to my double,
- we got a chance. - Se Hyun might do better...
- He might get 300 points. - and get 300 points.
That's right.
- I'll give it a go. - Give it a go.
(They decide to use one more shot on the gift certificates.)
If you fail...
I'll hold this.
- Let's do this. - Just get 100 points.
(This time, Jae Seok goes.)
- Just get 100 points. - He might get 300 points.
Just get 100 points.
We need a hero.
(Pressuring)
Heroes are born in difficult times.
That's right. It's true.
- We're in difficult times. - Let's do it.
- Here I go. - All right.
(If he gets more than 50 points, they'll get the gift certificates!)
- Go ahead. - Get 100 points.
- Don't be nervous. Just do it. - Let's do it.
- You got it. - Fifteen points.
Throw one more.
- No. - It's two points.
We can't keep going.
- No. We can't keep going. - It's two points.
(2 points)
(My goodness)
Two points.
- Shall we stop? - Stop.
(Professional: 108, Members: 61)
- Let's stop. - Let's stop.
(Remaining darts: 7)
He got two points. Let's stop.
He said "Here I go" so clearly.
- That dart... My goodness. - It's too bad.
- Seven darts remain. - It's too bad.
We're so close.
We need to give Chan Hee the gift certificates.
(Let's use one more shot.)
- If we had more darts... - Jae Seok.
Trust me this once.
- No. - You can't do it.
- I have a good feeling. - Trust me this once.
- You can't do it. - Next time.
- Next time. - We need 100 points.
(Bitter)
- Next time. - We'll win if we get 100 points.
Next time. This won't do.
We'll move on to the next round.
- This won't do. - You'll give up on this round.
(They give up on the gift certificates...)
- Let's practice. - Next time.
(with 7 darts remaining.)
- Let's practice. - It's too bad.
Se Hyun is too good at this.
- Let me practice. - Okay.
(They start practicing with Round 3 ahead.)
- Let's practice. - All right.
- Let's practice. - Let's do it.
Listen.
Jae Seok is keeping me in check.
He won't give me a chance.
I got a double,
and he got two points.
Seriously.
(Whining to the staff in the corner)
I can't believe it.
If you put a slow motion on me getting a double, it'll be so cool.
Don't do it.
What he did? Don't do it.
- What? - Jae Seok got two points.
Is that so?
But his form was very nice.
There you go.
(Reacting automatically)
(Jae Seok practices.)
But his form was very nice.
- You know... - I got the hang of it.
We... You got it.
- It's not about us doing well. - There you go.
You know...
Jae Seok. There you go. That's good.
(He begins to get his darts close to 100.)
Jae Seok. There you go.
- He got it. - Jae Seok.
(It looks like Jae Seok got the hang of it.)
- Se Hyun... - Let's go.
- That's good. - Let's hope that Se Hyun...
- will make a mistake. - I zeroed in.
(The end of practice)
- You zeroed in, right? - That's right.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's do this.
(It's the last round, Round 3.)
This is Round Three.
It's the last round...
- for the wild ginseng. - Let's go.
Wild ginseng!
- Let's do this. We can do it. - Okay.
(The last round with wild ginseng, Chan Hee's favorite, at stake)
- I'll do well this time. - Right now...
- Please go slow. - Hold it just once.
(Playing mind games)
You're too good at this.
(What's the last score of the pro the members must overcome?)
- We practiced a lot. - Se Hyun will go first.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Here I go. - Okay.
Se Hyun...
(The first dart)
I got the hang of it.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- My goodness. How tasty. - Gosh.
(100 points!)
- He didn't say, "Here I go." - He didn't say, "Here I go."
(Distracting)
He didn't say, "Here I go."
(Laughing)
- He didn't say, "Here I go." - He didn't say, "Here I go."
(Despite the distraction,)
- Se Hyun. - Yes, he did.
(he gets 100 points again!)
He didn't say, "Here I go."
- Se Hyun. - Yes, he did.
(It's the last shot.)
The next round,
he could get three hundred points.
(Will he get 300 points as Jong Kook has worried?)
- Yes, he did. - What should we do?
What should we do?
There we go. Thank goodness.
- Is the last one worth 6 points? - Is it 206 points?
(6 points)
- Yes, it's 206 points. - It's 206 points.
(The score they need to surpass for Round 3 is 206 points.)
- There we go. Thank goodness. - Is the last one worth six points?
(Professional: 206, Members)
- Six points. - It's 206 points.
- It's 206 points. - It's our turn.
(Remaining darts: 7)
We got this. Let's give it a try.
- We have a chance. - Jae Seok,
wouldn't it be better to have one person zero in...
- and keep going? - That's right.
- While that's the case... - Think about it.
(Suggesting one person throwing multiple darts)
- Taking turns hasn't helped. - One person... That's right.
One person in good condition...
- That's right. - should throw all the darts...
- and get the wild ginseng. - That's right.
I'm in very good condition.
- That won't work. - No.
He got the hang of it.
- He won't do well. - Hey.
- He got it. - That's good, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok)
Hey, he hasn't even thrown it.
- All right. Mr. Darts Bar. - What?
Seok Sam and I will throw the darts.
- All right. - Seok Sam and...
- Represent the team. - Give me one dart.
- Okay. - Give him one dart.
(Two aces and Haha are the final players.)
- One for him. Three for us two. - Okay.
I think I can do it.
Let's go. We need to give Chan Hee a present.
- Seriously. - Let's bring our hands together.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go. - All right.
- Let's go. - Haha.
(They set off to win the only gift remaining, the wild ginseng.)
- Seriously. - Here.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go. - In 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
Do it for real now.
- Let's go. - You got the hang of it, right?
- Go ahead. - Go ahead.
- Haha. - The weakest one should go first.
- I'll go last. - Go ahead.
No, you can't be the main character. Hurry up.
- Hobbit, go. - I hope...
(Here comes the Korean Hobbit.)
- I'll hit 100 points. - Good luck!
If you get 100 points...
- If you get 100 points... - Then you'll be a hero.
(Professional: 206, Members)
Haha, then you can throw the rest of the darts.
(Remaining darts: 7)
Haha, do it with confidence.
- You aren't that good at... - Do it with confidence.
(Upset)
Do it with confidence, okay?
- He'll get one point... - Do it with confidence.
(Talking behind him)
- or put it on the black part. - Go.
Seriously.
(Everyone looked down on Hobbit Ha throughout the match.)
- Do it with confidence. Go. - Okay.
(If he gets 100 points, he'll become a hero.)
- You'll get 100 points. - Go.
You'll get 100 points.
- What? - One point.
- It's 1 point. - How did you get 1 point?
- Hey. - Why...
- Hey. - Why did you give him a dart?
(Professional: 206, Members: 1)
- What's up with one point? - One point?
- It was close, right? - One point.
(Acting cute)
- Seriously. - Hey, it's too...
If you give me one more dart, I'll do an amazing job.
- No. - Forget it. Move out of the way.
Haha got one point.
(Remaining darts: 6)
- Shall we throw three darts... - Why did you give him a dart?
- at a time? - Go first.
(Seok Sam, who'll throw 3, steps up.)
- Shall we alternate? - I had a good form, right?
- Throw three, Seok Jin. - Really?
- You need to get the hang of it. - That's right.
- Get the hang of it. - If it looks like...
I'm not getting the hang of it,
- you should do it. - Okay. I'll do it.
Seok Jin, think about the past.
(Back when he used to go to the dart bar)
- Think about your days of youth. - The past. Okay.
Yong Man, that punk, laughed at me.
- That's right. - "You barely got..."
- "forty points." - Talk about your mom and dad.
- Your mom. - That's right.
(Seok Sam prayed to his late dad to avoid a penalty once.)
Dad!
Must we go that far?
Maybe you aren't that desperate.
- This is... - No, I'm desperate.
- Are you desperate? - I want to win.
I want to give him a present.
- Dad! - Nice.
(He pulled out his secret weapon once again.)
You're watching me, right, Dad?
Dad!
This is an important moment, Dad.
Why do I get so nervous and shaky at times like this?
Mom! Look over me, please!
(A letter to the skies)
(Will Seok Sam's Dad respond to his plea?)
- Dad... - Nice.
- Your father... - That was good.
- Dad! - That was good.
- Nice. - I think he'll score 100.
- Calling your dad was nice. - He'll score 100.
(Professional: 206, Members: 1 Remaining darts: 6)
- He'll score 100. - That was so funny.
Him calling his dad was so funny.
- Dad. - Dad.
He'll throw now.
- I miss Dad. - Dad.
It's Dad, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin's first shot)
Dad!
(It was so close. He got 14.)
- Fourteen points. - Fourteen points.
That's much better than before.
- This way... - Dad!
It's still not enough, Dad. That was a bit weak.
(Delivering an additional message)
(Professional: 206, Members: 15 Remaining darts: 5)
- That's funny. - That will do it.
- Your dad is watching over you. - Alright.
- Nice. - You're doing great right now.
(He needs to score 100 to catch up with the professional.)
- It's much better than before. - Dad's power.
It hit the middle.
Dad's power!
(Seok Sam's second shot)
If you scored 100, that would be crazy.
If that was so easy...
- No. - Just like before.
- I had a feeling. - Just like before.
(Professional: 206, Members: 30)
The last throw!
- Please hit 100. - It's going to hit the center now.
(Remaining darts: 4)
You should do this, Jae Seok.
- You should do it. - Keep going. You got this.
- A little to the right. - Dad... Mom, Mom!
Mom...
Go and call your mom.
(He sets off to the window side.)
Mom... Mom and Dad.
Call both your mom and dad.
Mom!
- Mom! - Mom...
It's Seok Jin!
Seok Jin...
I need to score 100 now, Mom.
Mom!
- "Please come out." - Nice.
(Recalling his mom as well)
Please come out for a moment during the meal, Mom!
It's a bit sad.
Isn't this a first?
(Crying)
- If I score 100 after doing that, - That would really be...
it will become an iconic moment.
If you score 100 after that, it will really be...
(Will he really get to score 100?)
No...
(9 points)
- Good. It can't be helped. - That was close.
(Professional: 206, Members: 39)
- Nine points. - Just forget about it.
- We'll do it now. Let's go. - That was so close.
(Remaining darts: 3)
- Let's go. - We have to score 100.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(The last person to go is Jae Seok.)
- You can do it. - We won't say anything.
- Let's go! - We won't even mention the score.
(The 1st shot of the final 3 darts)
It went well when I looked that way earlier.
If we get one more...
(Suggesting in the midst of all this)
Just like you did before.
We get triple points!
- Triple points. - Seventeen times three!
- Fifty... - How many points is that?
- What's the score? - Fifty-one.
(Pretending to calculate)
- Fifty-one! - Fifty-one, that's good!
(Jae Seok's 1st shot is 51!)
- Not bad. - Fifty-one.
(Professional: 206, Members: 90)
That wasn't intentional.
(Remaining darts: 2)
- If you score 100, - If I score 100...
our chances of winning go up.
(Jae Seok's second shot)
Just score 100.
That's a double.
- Fifteen times... - Thirty points.
- Thirty points. - Thirty points.
(Professional: 206, Members: 120)
If you score 100 now, we win.
It's the last shot.
(They have only 1 shot. They win if they score 100.)
- Come here. - Let's put our hands together.
- Come. - Let's do this.
- Chan Hee as well. - Come, Chan Hee.
We need to score 100. We need a miracle.
(Chan Hee joins in as well.)
If you score 100, we win.
If I score 100, we win. Let's do this.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
If you score 100, we win.
You could call your uncle, Jae Seok.
Uncle?
(What uncle?)
- Uncle... - My father is an uncle to you.
That uncle?
- Give him a call. - I met him before.
(It makes sense.)
Your father...
- Uncle... - Father, Mother! Remember me?
You used to feed me back when I lived in Suyu-ri.
- Right. Back when I was jobless. - Right.
(His son's friend is saying hello after a long time.)
- Please give me some strength. - Okay!
- Okay! - Please help me.
- Okay. - Let me score 100!
(The happy reunion comes to an end.)
Okay!
Let's go.
You emceed my brother's wedding as well.
- That's right. - Right.
(Professional: 206, Members: 120)
If you score 100, we win.
(Remaining darts: 1)
- That will be a miracle. - I'm not sure if it'll work.
It worked when I aimed for 20 earlier.
- Just throw it casually. - Casually.
Casually.
- You did it. - It's far.
(Jae Seok has shown exceptional skill...)
(in dart missions for years.)
- The 700th episode! - He'll get it by chance.
(Even during practice earlier)
Nice!
(He hit a 100, raising expectations.)
- He's a little shocked. - He's shocked.
(Professional: 206, Members: 120)
It worked when I aimed for 20 earlier.
- Just throw it casually. - Casually.
(Remaining darts: 1)
(Will he be able to score 100...)
- Casually. - One hundred points.
(with his back against the wall?)
Looks good!
(He threw it!)
(13 points)
(Professional: 206, Members: 133)
That's a bummer.
(Remaining darts: 0)
- If it had gone a little... - That was so close.
- That was close. - You failed Round Three.
(Joint supplement, fail, Onnuri gift certificates, fail)
(They failed in Round 3 as well.)
- This... - Goodness.
(He can't let go.)
- Goodness. - I'm really good at this.
I had gotten the hang of it.
What a shame.
(Feeling disappointed)
It didn't work.
I'm sorry, but as a last chance,
- What? - could you give Haha seven tries...
- How does that sound? - A real battle?
(Suggesting Haha play a bonus round)
- Could you give him a chance? - Sure.
- Okay. - He's gotten the hang of it.
- Seven darts! - If you fail,
- you'll pay for it yourself. - Okay.
Good.
(They accept the suggestion with his money at stake.)
- Haha will pay for it himself. - Haha...
is so upset about it.
(K-Hobbit revived.)
This is worth 500 dollars.
If Haha succeeds,
- we'll just give it to him, - Nice.
(Bonus round)
(If Haha wins, the staff will pay for the gift.)
and if he fails,
(If the staff wins, Haha will pay for the gift.)
- he'll be the one to pay for it. - Okay!
I'll buy it for you!
(I'd love that.)
- Nice! - Two hundred points!
- Your hands were shaky earlier. - Score more than 206 points.
(Bonus game, Professional: 206, Haha)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
The chances are not bad.
(He makes an attempt right away.)
(He threw a 100!)
- Stay still. - Did he score 100?
(Surprised)
- Goodness. - Stay still.
(Bonus game, Professional: 206, Haha: 100, Remaining darts: 6)
(Breathing)
- Good. - Stay still.
(He makes his second throw right away.)
- Stay still. - What's going on?
- Slowly. - Take your time, Haha.
- Take your time! - What's going on?
- Take your time. - Take your time.
(3 points)
Take your time!
- Take your time! - You can do it!
(Breathing)
- Take your time! - Aim higher!
(2 points)
Take your time!
- Take your time! - Take your time.
(Goodness)
(Bonus game, Professional: 206, Haha: 108)
(1 of the last 3 darts)
Take your time.
- Take your time. - That's still...
(20 points)
- That's not bad. - Take your time.
- That's still... - Hold on. Wait.
- That's still 20 points. - How many points is it?
(Checking the interim score)
What's the score now?
- What's the score now? - Take it slow, Haha.
(Fuming)
(Screaming)
(Haha is extremely excited.)
What's the score?
Father!
Twenty-eight. One hundred. One hundred twenty-eight?
(Bonus game, Professional: 206, Haha: 128)
(Remaining darts: 2)
- You win if you score 100. - You win if you score 100!
You have two darts left, and you win if you score 100.
(If he focuses a bit more, this will work.)
- You win if you score 100. - You win if you score 100.
You have two darts left.
- You can do it, Haha. - Why did you get so excited?
(Babbling on)
- You just threw the others weirdly. - It's 128 points.
It's 128 points.
(He has 2 darts left.)
- Right? - It's 128 points.
- You have 128 points. - If you score 100...
You win if you score 100.
You have two darts left, Haha!
(Breathing)
You can do it.
I like that look.
- Nice. - Scoring 100 is the only option.
(Hitting)
Hold on!
(He made a big mistake at a critical moment.)
- That doesn't count. - You have one dart left.
- No. - You can't do that.
- You can't do that. - That was really bad.
(Bonus game, Professional: 206, Haha: 128)
(Remaining darts: 1)
You can't do that, Haha. You have one dart left.
(He has only one dart left.)
Let's go!
Haha!
My money!
- It's the last dart. - Haha.
(To save 500 dollars,)
- Haha. - Haha.
(he needs to score higher than 80.)
- Haha... - Haha...
(He threw it.)
(20 points)
- Goodness. - Okay.
(Goodness)
Okay.
(That means...)
- Okay. - Haha...
- Haha will pay 500 dollars! - Haha will pay for it!
(Ha Dong Hoon will pay 500 dollars!)
Haha will pay for it. This is a happy ending.
(Thanks for the wild ginseng.)
It's a happy ending.
You'll be able to get the ginseng.
(It's a happy ending anyway.)
- We'll be able to give him that. - Haha...
- After he got 100 points, - He's happy.
he got carried away.
- He got way too hyped. - Did you see his face?
(A textbook case of fragile mindset)
After getting 100 points, he was like this.
He wanted to be a hero.
We thank Lee Se Hyun again for joining us today.
(We thank Pro Lee Se Hyun for showcasing his 9-dart masterclass.)
Thank you.
I'll wire the money right away.
(The 500 dollars)
So, here are the results.
(The dart game has come to an end.)
Though you failed all three rounds of the games of darts,
(Although they lost all 3 rounds,)
in the bonus round,
(Haha used his money to give wild ginseng to Chief Kang.)
Haha agreed to buy the wild ginseng with his own money.
He's sending the money now.
- I sent the money. - Really?
Do you have the production crew's bank account numbers?
- Why do you have them? - It's the mobile payment.
It's the mobile payment.
(Sad)
He just spent 500 dollars in a flash.
(Excited)
He spent 500 dollars in less than 2 minutes.
(The one who paid for the gift presents it to Chan Hee.)
This is so nice.
(Bowing)
Stay healthy with this wild ginseng.
- I'll keep working hard. - This is so heartwarming.
- I'll get you the joint supplement. - This is beautiful.
Now, we will officially present...
the custom chair and wild ginseng to him.
(Final gift for Chief Kang: Director's chair and wild ginseng)
Let's take a photo together here.
- Let's take a photo. - Hold the wild ginseng.
(Wrapping up with a souvenir photo with the gift in his arms)
We will stand behind you like a big family portrait.
One, two, three.
(We thank the immortal Chief Kang, who will keep running with us.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Two absolute outlaws are coming to shake up...
the peaceful 2026 guest scene.
Won Hun is here.
It's Eun Bi.
- You're from KBS? - Yes.
He's our direct junior.
(Keeping him in check)
I didn't think you were an officially recruited comedian.
When you auditioned, the competition ratio was....
- only like 2 on 1, right? - Isn't it itchy?
(A monster birthed by YouTube who has no respect even to seniors)
(The far junior who ruthlessly takes down Seok Sam)
- You might end up passing out. - We're in a bus.
I'll pass on the prize if I can be a regular here.
(Mutiny specialist and outlaw, Kim Won Hun)
While pretending to be innocent,
(A recurring guest specializing in backstabbing...)
(behind an innocent face)
- she betrayed us all. - She stabbed us in the back.
You didn't seem too happy to see me today.
(Upset)
My memories with you aren't so great.
(A PTSD trigger)
Really?
Do you have some cash on you?
- Why do you ask? - Why?
(An expert in extorting the members)
There's a drive-thru here.
- Can you buy us one? - We don't have time.
(She effortlessly wraps the members around her finger.)
- Something refreshing. - Nice.
(Running Man's dedicated outlaw, Kwon Eun Bi)
- She's aiming for Waterbomb. - She's aiming for Waterbomb.
(Self-absorbed)
- I'm so good at playing games. - Won Hun.
- Slow down. - Slow down.
- It's the flow of the game! - Won Hun.
(Those fighting to stop the outlaws' rampage)
- Okay. - Slow down.
(Those ready to run wild)
(An inevitable clash between them)
He got it.
(Grunting)
Your belly button is dry.
(Hands-on skin care)
Get him.
(For those who break the law of Running Man,)
- Okay. - Warning.
It's not me.
(there's no mercy.)
- What's with him? - What are you doing?
(The fierce survival brawl of natural-born outlaws)
That's too much!
(Will You Do It or Not?)
(Running Man)